Alright.
Seems like this one’s nice and remote.
Won’t take us too long to-
WHAT THE F-
What the fuck are these things?!
I want to say these are earth goats, sir.
I don’t care how great they
are, they are In. My. Way!
¡¿Que esta pasando!?
(What's going on!?)
¡¿Que carajo!?
(What the Hell!?)
Nice! Easy, easy goats! Easy!
El Chupacabras!
Shit! Scatter!
Run you stretched asshole!
Dammit!!
Augh!!
Pendejo que te voy a arrancar la cabeza-
(You IDIOT, I'm gonna tear your fucking head off-)
la Chupacabra de mierda esta...
(piece of shit Chupacabra...)
Ay caramba, he brought the big guns.
Come on gang, we lost the element of
surprise, let’s just get 'em tomorrow.
You got it, sir.
Wooooah- let's go Millie!
Augh!
Mmmm, eughh.
What the...
Eff?!
¡Vengan todos!
(Come one, come all!)
¡Señoras y Señores!
(Ladies and gentleman!)
¡Pásenle, pásenle!
(Step right up, step right up!)
¡Vengan a ver un AUTÉNTICO Chupacabra!
(Come and see an AUTHENTIC Chupacabra!)
Only a hundred pesos!
To see a real chupacabras
caught by ME last night.
A chupa what!?
Look buddy, I’ll have you
know that I am a dignified-
No hablo Inglés.
What? You were just speaking-
Everyone!
Watch this monstruo
suck the blood from the goat!
Bleh!! Urgh!
Look asshole!
The only sucking I do is on cocks-
EUGH!
Not that kind!
Pussies-
FUCK!
Dammit I’m doing a bit!
And cloacas, ah…
Now if you don’t mind I-
OH!! I’M GONNA PUT YOU
IN THE FUCKING GROUND!
Hang on.
Fuuuuuuuuck me.
Alright.
We gotta secure the scene.
We heard that there’s a real "chupacabra" here?
Yes, over here!
Hundred pesos please.
Señor, we are with the government.
Hundred.
Pesos.
Right.
So uhhh…
How much is that?
Five dollars and sixty nine cents.
Uhh, you have any cash on you?
Who has cash anymore?
You paid the tip with cash
at brunch the other day.
Yeah, that’s all I had.
Why don’t you pay him?
I bought us the coffee this morning.
Are you really pulling that card in
front of this fine man and his fine goats?
No, what? I literally never have cash in my life.
You're always the one who pays cash.
Hey, hey psst!
Yeah, I know I killed some
of your family earlier,
but if you help me out of this little pickle
I’ll make it up to you little fella!
Sooo, can you take caaard, or-
OW!
Ffff-uck, you stupid goat!
YOU INSULT MY
GOOOAT?!
YOU PAY WITH YOUR
LIIIIIIIIFE!
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wooahhh.
Heyyyy.
Estoy. muerto.
(I'm... dead.)
Bleh.
Oh dear god.
DEMON GUN!!
Hey, thatta boy!
Hey dipshits!
Remember me?
It’s him!
Get him!
Chupacabra!
Yaaay! ¡Me gustaaa!
(Yaaay! I like iiiit!)
Yeah, bitch!
I’m the fucking "chupra-ca-dupra"-
and I’m here
to fuck you aaaall.
Oh my god, everybody run!
He’s got a gun!
¡¡Aye dio mío!! ¡¡¡Tiene pistola!!!
(Oh my god!! He has a gun!!!)
Agent one! Get over here!
We got badges, we're legit!
We’re important!
Get out of our way!
No! More goats!
Oh my god, run!
What are you do-
Do NOT trip, do not trip!
Come on!
AHHH! Too many goats!!!
Oh, too many goats!!
Oh my god, more goats!
Amazing work there lil' buddy.
You really helped my little red ass out.
And for that I’m making you an
honorary I.M.P V.I.P uh… associate.
Here, have a sticker. Ha ha! Nyonk!
Later!