Eeeeee!
Psst. Mills, over here!
Ew! Get off of me!
Sister!
You finally made it out!
After I asked you like a billion times!
Lucky for you, a billion and one was the sweet spot to visit this trash heap.
You ain't even been here before!
Come on, I got the whole day planned out!
Wow, the whole day!
You ain't gotta.. run off with your princess to axe some Earth fella?
Nah.
Business has been slow lately.
So, the boys say they've got it covered!
Damn, ain't I special!
Where are we startin'?
We'll...uh...
start with a day spa, and some shoppin'...
No offense, Sal, but you smell like hog ass.
I do not, Prissy Miss probably bathes regular!
Oh! Uh, no. No, yep. You're right that's-
that is definitely hog ass.
Come on!
Let's tear this town to shreds!
Yee-fuckin'-haw!
So y'all, pay to soak in mud here?
Well, it's "special" mud.
It's relaxing.
How bout' this one?
Nice one, Mills.
Ah...
See?
Best day ever, right?
I told you you'd enjoy yourself!
Yeah, yeah.. I guess this place ain't so bad.
Ain't so bad? It's awesome!
Uh-huh...
One day isn't even enough.
There are so many exciting things to show-
Heh, yeah, I mean,
with so many exciting things here,
it's no wonder you never make your way back home.
SHIT! That slipped out.
..What?
You know... the Wrath Ring,
all that dirt and rust and boring nothingness.
Not much of a thriving club scene down there, why is it that, right?
I was there at the last Harvest Moon Festival!
I mean, sure, for your fancy job.
You showed up with that blue-blooded bird, your dick-swingin' boss,
that cupcake husband of yours, and...
I don't know!
I couldn't really see how I'd fit into this shiny new life you built.
Sal...
I'm sorry.
Things get real crazy and busy over here, and...
You think things didn't get busier for me
back home when you decided to scooch?
I've basically been running the place solo!
Honestly, Mills,
today was great.
Better than great.
It reminded me of how we used to be like this
damn near every day before you left.
I hate to think that it'll be even longer
before we see each other again.
Yeah...
I miss that too.
There's always room in my life for my sister, Sallie May.
I'm sorry I ain't been back home as much as I'd like.
I'll try harder.
But... you know...
the boys are older now.
Ma and Daddy got plenty of extra hands at the ranch.
You could come visit more often too!
I think I'd like that.