Aw, thanks Mills, but-
I don’t think I need back up to take
down some suburban, college girl.
You enjoy that bullshit musical,
and stop trying to use me as
an excuse to get out of it-
Hey, look.
If I had to sit through that miserable,
French hog shit well so do you, okay?
Bye, Mills!
Oh ho, ho. Bingo.
"B-Y-N-G-O"
♪ I love killing, shooting
things, I’ll use a saw! I’ll use a fork, too! ♪
♪ Da dun, da da. ♪
♪ I love killing things
with any kind of weapon, ♪
♪ give me a knife and I’ll kill someone ♪
♪ and today it’s gonna be a stupid bitch! ♪
♪ Da da- ughn!
Oof!!
Ow! What the fuck?!
AHH!
Oh!
Oooh.
Ugh, must be watching them
damn “hen-tays” again.
Why won’t she leave?!
Oh my god!
What... are you?
I’m your worst fucking nightmare, bitch!
Fuck. How are you doing this? What is that?!
It’s official merch from "Akuma no Otto".
It’s the pendant given to
Setsuki in episode 5-6-9
that protects its wearer from-
wait are you a demon? Like…
a real demon?
Yeah, basically. Look, where
did you even get something like-
A demon?
Here to steal a little kitten like me?
Forced to be part of your
demonic harem, "blushes".
Huh.
Why d'you think I would
do something like that?
Ohhhh, you’re one of those.
So what’s your name?
Uhhh.
Blitzø.
What are you gonna do to me, Blitzy-kun?
Uh. Apparently nothing
while you’re wearing that.
I don’t feel like myself.
Are- are you...
putting some sort of-
nasty spell over me?
What? No, I’m literally
just standing here, lady.
If you say so, master.
I mean...
daddy.
But when you look into my eyes,
it’s like I have no control over my...
No!
Ahh-haaah, 'kaaay.
You demonic brute!
I’m too pure a heart for you to corrupt!
Oh, thank fucking Satan.
Satan?
Is that your lord?
The one you plan to offer
me to as a sexual sacrifice?
But once you have me, you realize
you could never go through with it
because I’m the only woman who
could ever make you feel something
after the loss of your wife!
Your wife-
who was the first one your
lord Satan took as a concubine.
But now you’d rather have me!
And you’d rather fight him to the death
than allow me to come to the same fate!
Ew. Lady look, I was sent
here to kill you, alright?
You were a bitch online one time,
someone didn’t like it,
they put a hit on you,
I know it’s excessive but I
don’t make the rules, oh well.
You want to kill...
Meee?
Oh yeah. Even more now.
Of course!
You want to take my mortal soul to Hell
so that we can be together forever!
Look, whatever gets you there.
Can you just take off the
necklace and hand over my knife.
Yes master!!
No, I mustn't.
But I want you!
My soul...
but I’m destined for this!
Bitch, can we hurry this up?
OHHHHH YESSS!
Thanks.
Make it quick, my demon prince!
Eugh. Can you please stop
enjoying this so much? Fuck.
I will see you...
on the other side...
my-
Blitzy-kun.
Stab. Stab stab.
Hey, yeah, it’s done.
So you can go ahead and
wire me that money now,
and I’ll go ahead and never think
about this night ever again.
I’m here, Blitzy-kuuun!!
I saw your billboard!
I’m here for you my love!
I’ll be by your side forever!
BLITZY-KUUUN!!!!