That was a big jump!
Christ on a stick, I’m freezing
my little red cock off!
Where is that thing
supposed to be?
The client said it was
near the research station.
Th-th-th-that research station?
Oh crumbs,
that can’t be good.
Oh shi-yikes. Yeah.
What happened here?
These guys were torn to shreds.
I’ve seen wrath b-b-beasts
less brutal than this.
What and or who could’ve done this?
Uh, that. Probably.
Okay, Moxxie, get up top,
Millie, cover the entrances.
I got it here.
Yes, sir.
Hey- y-you got him Mox?
Yes, sir!
Sweet,
let’s turn him into some SWISS cheese!
[Shaky inhale]
[Slow exhale]
Guess he met his match, heh heh.
Eat shit in Hell polar slut!
Good job Mox, now let’s get
out of this frozen fuck-hole.
Hold it, Blitzø.
Look at these marks!
They weren’t made by no bullets.
And here-
bitemarks.
Shhhhit.
Uh what, what’s the problem?
This slut wasn’t running toward us.
He was running away.
From something else.
Look!
Drop him!
Shit.
Fuck, that’s like ten!
Well...
Maybe those ones are nice.
They’re not!
RUN!
Mox, come on!
Sir, uh, could you get us out of here!?
Fucking wrist crystal!
What’s the hold up, Blitzø?
We- I can’t just make it go, okay? I’m
still getting used to this fucking thing!
God- ugh.
Damn it, damn it, damn it,
damn it, damn it, damn it!
It’s from Lust!
You can’t just brute force it!
FUCK!
You gotta treat it right,
caress it.
I don’t know I- ugh!
I’ve never been good at this shit!
Use your tongue!
How do you not know how to do this?
Moxxie, I’m a fucking top!
T-T-Try spelling the alphabet.
"A"... uh, um- "C- B!"
With your tongue!
Oh, I knew that.
"A", "B", "C", and "D"
Oh for Satan’s sake.
Oh damn.
I taught him that.
Can we go, please?
Eat this, bitches! Hah!