I was a good person before it all went down.
I was good my entire life.
Good morning!
I hope you all did your homework!
♪ We love to do our homework ♪
♪ and we love our teacher too ♪
♪ Then when I throw up these fun questions ♪
♪ you should know just what to do ♪
♪ Okay! ♪
♪ 2 + 6 is 8 ♪
♪ and good behavior is great ♪
♪ and it's now the part of the class where we ♪
♪ say the time of day and date ♪
♪ It's 9 in the morning ♪
♪ on January 8th ♪
♪ The sun is out, smiling ♪
♪ and it's your husband's birthday ♪
♪ La la la la ♪
♪ Lalalalala ♪
Oh my stars!
Stop singing, children.
Hush up now!
I forgot it's my husband's birthday!
I didn't get him anything special.
Maybe if we call him we can do a happy birthday surprise!
Okay! Oh yeah!
Right there.
Right there. Oh yeah.
Ow! That's actually my asshole.
- But I don't care. Yeah!
- Not there, not there.
- Put it in!
- Okay, yeah.
Wait! Mrs Mayberry!
Remember what you taught us?
Think before you act.
- Okay...
Oh, shit!
Sweetie, what are you doing here?
- Shut up, Jerald!
[SCREAMS]
You scream like a bitch!
- Oh, God.
What have you done?
She had a family!
- We could've had a family!
[GUN SHOTS]
Oh, dear God. What have I done?
In front of you all! I'm so sorry, my children.
Don't forget to work on your timetables!
[GUN SHOT]
You do everything right in life.
Play by all the rules,
and still get sent down here with all
the Hitlers and Epsteins of the world.
After one measly massacre propelled by blind rage.
So that's why I'm here.
To get my revenge.
I mean, was she hotter?
I'm just saying, I'm having a hard time understanding
the unprompted mellow-drama you just spat at me, tits.
Anyway, I'm don't think you quite understand how
we're operating down here.
You see, we take revenge out on the living
and it sounds like the core-cast of your sitcom
of a death frankly are all probably down here
in hell with you.
Boop!
Not all of them.
The whore survived.
Now they all call her a hero.
How does it feel to have survived such a crazy bitch?
I just hope that sick woman finally found peace.
You are so brave. Here's 2 million dollars.
Oh! Thank you!
Between the talk shows and donation bullshit
she made so much goddamn cash;
getting shot was the best thing to happen to her.
You're a hero!
You're a hero, girl!
My mama's a hero!
She is a hero!
[MOANS] You're a hero!
You're a hero.
She is not a hero!
Mhm, okay, yeah.
My thoughts exactly.
Moxxie, stop shaking.
You're gonna shoot our only hellhound.
Wow, I feel so loved here.
Just take a deep breath and let it out.
But... it's a family.
Under what circumstances would we ever need
to kill a human family?
I mean, if that's what the client wants...
Maybe like a shitty dad...
or a mob family...
that's understandable.
but to eradicate an entire innocent,
seemingly innocent in this instance,
upper middle class family bloodline?!
Hey! You don't know they're innocent!
This kid probably sets dogs on fire.
Maybe this girl gets off to bullying Australian kids online,
and this guy.... this guy definitely watches.
Exactly! Humans are full of secret nasties.
It's why so many of them end up here.
- But!
- Guilty and innocent aren't our business, Mox.
Killing who we're paid to is our business.
Shoot the target.
I just think it's a bit excessive
and we could be a bit more selective, is all.
Guys, I want you to meet...!
Our newest client.
Damn it, Moxxie!
I just bought those eels!
Bye, and don't worry we'll get that skank
in less than 24 hours or your first kill is free!
When did we start implementing that deal?
When you set fire to my office in front of a client,
YOU FUCKING DICKSHIT!
Now someone please tell me that fancy book is still intact!
You mean, our only ticket to the other side?
Yeah, got it.
And that's why you're my favorite, Loonie.
You get a treat now.
Ew, stop.
Ah, Nom.
You're so gross.
Oh, stop it. I get enough of that from my therapist.
Now let's go lick some ass!
The expression is kick some ass, Blitzø.
Mine's better.
Oh, fuck.
That's got to be her.
[LAUGHS] This is too easy.
Moxxie, do you want this one?
- Me?
- Yeah, this one's simple enough for you to handle.
It's just a happy mother who just got out of
the hospital.
Snooze you loose, Mox.
And I got you, bitch.
Wait, are we actually killing a family?
Now don't be a puss. We're just killing a mother.
We're ruining a family.
But! Hold on.
Let's just think about it.
What was that, Ralphie?
I don't know, Martha.
But whatever it is, they're gonna be tomorrow night's dinner.
Alright, kids. Guns out!
Looks like we got some rabbits to catch, youngin's.
What the fuck was that, Moxxie?!
[COUGHS]
I'm sorry. They just seemed so wholesome and happy.
I panicked.
Oh, who the fuck is innocent, Moxxie.
From the moment of birth you're already a parasite
leeching off your mama's tits.
Get the fuck over yourself, you baby dick prick.
Ow! A new hole!
Scatter!
Where you go, little critter?
Y'all can't hide long from me.
[GROWLS]
Oh, well, hello little ones.
Aren't you cute?
It's nice to have a new critter to play with.
Oh, crumbs.
[CACKLES]
I know you're hurting, little devil.
I promise I can take that pain go away real quick.
Just come let mumma Martha put a bullet
in your pretty little skull.
Stolas, this is a really bad time.
Oh, when isn't it a bad time, Blitzy?
What is it?
I've been meaning to follow up in our
last little conversation regarding my Grimoire.
What did you just call me?
My book, Blitzy.
The book I was given to do my job?
That I have allowed you to use to do yours?
I can hear you, darling!
Shit!
Anyhoo, I have been thinking.
You know I have been permitting you to
access the mortal realm less than legally for
some time now, but
I do need it back to fulfill my duties.
I was thinking...
What if we worked out some kind of exchange?
Favors for favors.
Doesn't that sound... enticing?
You gotta stop using your fancy ass rich people talk, okay?
I'm trying to concentrate on not getting fucked in my "A".
Then let me keep it simple.
Once a month on the full moon, you return the book
to me followed by a night of passionate fornication,
and you get to keep it all the rest of the time.
Hm? Sound fair, my little imp?
Fine, whatever.
Oh, Blitzø.
I'm so excited!
I cannot wait to feel your slimy c*ck inside of my a*s.
Gotcha!
So you're a little devil, huh?
Come to drag me and my kin to hell?
Well, not today Satan!
Gonna send y'all back where he came from.
Millie!
I had that fucking shot.
Goddamn it, Moxxie.
Satan, we return your filthy creatures back
to the pits of hell.
May the root of evil remain honored as we continue thou work!
Yeah, that's not exactly how it works, lady.
Sorry, your fire doesn't really hurt us but...
I mean, I could fake it if that'll get your dick hard.
Oh... shit!
Well, I'll just shoot you in your smart ass mouth.
That would be more effective.
Blitzø!
[CACKLES]
[GUN SHOT]
Moxxie!
You're not getting your goddamn paycheck for this one, Mox.
Oh yeah, thanks. I'm fine.
I'm sorry, sir.
I compromised our objective and put us in harm's way.
It won't happen again. I promise
Apology accepted.
But if you ever pull a stunt like this again
I will fuck you and your wife.
Alrighty, job well done.
Now let's get off.
Eh, yeah. Give me a moment.
I need to get something I left at the house.
Okay, fine but hurry up.
Loona, we're ready to come home, dear.
While you and I [Bleep!]...
Jelly sandwiches... All night...
Don't move.
What are you gonna do, little guy?
Kill us?
I should. You people are monsters,
but you should have a chance at a life and a purpose.
Look at your children. They have their whole
future ahead of them.
You are going to face your crimes justly.
I will call your earthly authorities and they will
make sure you are dealt with fairly.
I'm handling this my way.
Oh shit.
Uh, do you, uh...
Do you have a phone to summon 911?
Yeah, it's in the kitchen.
Then... what is this for?
It's a universal remote. Got it for the kids.
Awww.
There he is. Had a good wank-off session, Moxxie?
Excuse me?
Look, I don't care where you cum in the living world
just "cum" to your job on time, alright?
See you at the office.
You doing okay, sweetie?
Better now, honey.
I think I just needed a minute to process.
You have a good heart, honey.
Just a fuzzy head.
We got 'em, boys!
Did you see that little Mox, Moxxie?
Did it! Oh, Moxxie!
Well, here's to another mission accomplished,
and Moxxie finally learned not to fuck up.
And killing people isn't that big a deal if
they try to kill you back.
That's messed up...
But I paid for it.
Yeah, fuck that family.