Mommy! Daddy!
Mmph. Via's calling us, Stella.
You get up.
[SIGH]
Via? What troubles you, my owlette?
Daddy, daddy.
I had a dream!
A really bad dream.
A nightmare.
I was looking all over the palace,
and I couldn't find you anywhere.
You weren't there.
There, there, Via.
It's okay, you're okay.
When you're scared and you don't know where I am,
you must remember no matter what happens to me
I will never be far away from my special little starfire.
♪ It always seems more quiet ♪
♪ In the dark ♪
♪ It always feels so stark ♪
♪ How silence grows under the moon ♪
♪ Constellations gone so soon ♪
♪ I used to think that I was bold ♪
♪ I used to think love would be fun ♪
♪ Now all my stories have been told ♪
♪ Except for one ♪
♪ As the stars start to align ♪
♪ I hope you take it as a sign ♪
♪ That you'll be okay ♪
♪ Everything will be okay ♪
♪ And if the seven rings collapse ♪
♪ Although the day could be my last ♪
♪ You will be okay ♪
♪ When I'm gone you'll be okay ♪
♪ And when creation goes to die ♪
♪ You can find me in the sky ♪
♪ Upon the Lost day ♪
♪ And you will be okay ♪
[STELLA]
I can't believe you slept with an imp...!
in our fucking bed!
[STOLAS]
It wasn't expected.
I didn't have time to go to a motel.
[STELLA]
A motel?
Like a fucking plebeian?
♪ My world is burning down around me ♪
[SCREAMS]
You want to fuck this one too?
No! Of course not.
You are a goddamn embarrassment.
I'm not spending another moment looking at your
pathetic, imp sucking face.
You're useless.
[SIGHS]
Good morning, Octavia!
Did you sleep well, my owlette?
Is that a serious question?
[NERVOUS] Mhm...
What's that you're listening to?
This song is called "My world is burning down around me".
It's by "F-ck You Dad"... it's a band.
Oh... how charming.
So you two done screaming for the day?
Uhm...
You know what I haven't done in a long, long time?
I haven't taken you to your favorite place in all of Hell!
Why don't we go to Loo Loo Land?
I'm not five anymore.
You always were so happy when I
took you to Loo Loo Land.
What do you say we go there again?
Have a day, just the two of us.
I'd rather kill myself.
There we go.
Anything but staying in this house.
Now, I'll arrange our security.
Security for a theme park?
We're rich and we're hot.
People want our money and our bodies.
Money maybe.
Speak for yourself, princess.
Now, I'm calling the only man who can f*ck me!
What?
Who can protect me... Us...
Being a part of the Goesha family
is rather valuable, you know.
[GROANS]
Oh, Blitzø. You're such a good boss.
Yeah! I really want you, sir!
Me too!
Let's three-way!
WHAT?!
Why hello, my big dicked Blitzy~
- What
- The
- Fuck
- Dad!
Language, everyone!
I have a special request.
Oh, look I just had a chemical peel so you'll have
to find someone else's face to plant
that feathered ass.
It's for my daughter.
Ah, well make sure she washes it.
No! No. No no no.
I'm taking my daughter to Loo Loo Land
and I was hoping you brave little imps would accompany us.
We're assassins, not bodyguards, okay?
Don't invite us to shit unless someone's gonna die.
I'll pay you.
Pay me what?
Money.
Done!
M&M, get in here! We're going to Loo Loo Land!
- Loo Loo Land?
Loo Loo Land!
SHUT THE FUCK UP!
Now remember, this is work and work only.
Me and my crew are not here to satisfy your
perverted bird needs, alright?
Hey, dad. Do we have to...
Okay, hold on right there, sweetie.
If you try fucking my little ass in that park, I swear to...
You are so cute when you are serious.
I'm literally gonna be sick.
Oh, crumbs. I knew today would be a lot.
What do you need?
Antacids? Ibuprofen? Morphine?
That was figurative, old man.
Oh, right.
But she said it was literal.
Wow, I haven't been to this place since I was a tot.
It hasn't changed a bit.
Oh, look!
It's Big Woobly.
That is deeply upsetting.
Oh, come on. It's fun!
You've never been here?
No. Theme parks always disturbed me,
especially the mascots.
Well, hey there!
[SCREAMS]
I'm Loo Loo. Welcome to Loo Loo Land.
If y'all get hurt here, just try to sue us.
Look, Via. It's Loo Loo.
I have a question.
Well, ask away little girlie.
Is it this park is just a really shameless spin-off
of Lucifer's far more popular Lu Lu World?
No?
This place reeks of insecure corporate shame.
[NERVOUS GIGGLE]
Why don't we go check out the rides?
That chick's creepy, huh?
Yeah, wait 'till her dad tries to diddle your holes.
What's that mean?
Don't talk to me!
I know you're a pervert under there.
Yeah...
You really like this place, huh?
I love this place.
My parents would bring me and my siblings here when they could swing it.
Money-wise.
Yeah, the prices do seem rather criminal.
I mean, that much for a novelty cup
that you'll use one time?
'Cause it's Loo Loo Land!
Listen to your hoe, Mox.
How about I take the first watch while you two
have a little fun.
[SQUEALS]
We gotta do my favorite ride!
Oh yeah? Wh- which one?
Oh, crumbs.
You know, it's quite thrilling to see you on the job, Blitzy.
Save it, bitch. I'm working.
You both need to get a room.
Hey! I am not a day hooker.
What? I just said I'm not one, prude.
Oh, look, Via!
You used to cry such tears of joy at this show.
Oh, no.
[DEMONIC LAUGHTER]
- I hate that fucking clown.
Oh, Blitzy!
I need my bodyguard, please.
Hey, implings! It's me, the Robotic Fizzarolli.
Shipped from Big Ozzie's Factory to bring
you a wonderful show celebrating
Loo Loo Land (spelled with O's to avoid lawsuits)
Hit it!
♪ Loo Loo Land
Loo Loo Land ♪
♪ Everybody sing along with the Loo Loo Band ♪
♪ Every boy, every girl
Every woman, every man ♪
♪ loves Loo Loo Land! ♪
♪ Loo Loo Land
Loo Loo Land ♪
♪ Everything is beautiful in Loo Loo Land ♪
♪ Ugly children holding hands ♪
♪ In Loo Loo Land ♪
♪ Everybody's friendly,
and nobody is mean ♪
♪ No copyright infringement's ever seen ♪
♪ I have a dream (He has a dream)
I'm here to tell (He's here to tell)♪
♪ About a magical fantastic place
called Loo Loo Land ♪
Hello, hello. Step right up and win a thing.
Oh, look Moxxie! A thing!
Oh, you like that thing?
Yes. I don't really know what that thing is
but I want that "thang".
Ah, finally some"thing" I can handle.
Okay, one game please.
Ohh, strike one little man.
But I hit it.
Hm, I don't know what to tell you, buddy.
The target, see, it didn't go down.
So yeah! No go, bro.
[GROWLS]
The heavens wrong with this thing?
Oh man, a real shame I tell ya.
Waa Waa.
Another!
♪-body sing along with the Loo Loo Band ♪
♪ Every body, every girl
Every woman, every man ♪
♪ loves Loo Loo Land ♪
[LAUGHS]
Oh, ho ho ho. How delightful.
Oh, my. What good aim you have, Blitzy.
Ugh, I can't do this anymore.
Wait- E-... Octavia!
[LAUGHS]
[GLITCHING]
Is that Blitzo my sensors spot up there?
I guess the kiddies are still running away from you, huh?
The 'O' is silent now.
Awww, just like your audience always was
when you told your lazy jokes here.
Bitch, I make more money killing people
than you do being a cheap-ass robo-rip-off
of an overrated sell-out jester.
[GLITCHING]
Ooo, someone's salty.
Real or not, though. People love me.
Does anybody love you, Blitzo?
No.
But I'm really good with guns now.
Dance, bitch!
Torches! I say I say, get your inconvenient torches here!
Ow!
I say ow!
[CACKLES]
Wow, man you're really starting to make this sad.
You know, if you suck you suck.
Guess you won't win your honey here a prize.
Let me try.
Oh, look at that. Lucky shot, baby.
Are you kidding me?
You- you- you charlatan!
Hey, uh, get lost, pipsqueak. I'm talkin' to the lady~
OWWWW! Oof! Auuugh!
Sir?!
Ohhh, hey, guys! You should probably go,
uh, make sure Stolas is okay. I've...
got some unfinished business to take care of.
Oh, what a mouth!
Goddammit, Nathan!
You ruined another bloody photo!
Why were you even born?!
Octavia?
Just leave me alone!
Octavia!
Umm, I think I'm supposed
to be bodyguarded right now!
Ugh, that's better. Where is Blitzy?
He's my knight in shining armor, not you littler ones.
He's, uhhhh... busy.
Being a fool.
What kind of fool?
The "everything is now on fire" kind.
Octavia...
I take it you are... not having fun.
I didn't even want to come here!
I'm sorry, sweetie. I... I thought you loved it here.
When I was a kid and my parents didn't hate each other...
and my dad didn't flirt with some...
weird red dickhead the entire time.
I'm sorry, Via. I'm sorry for... everything...
happening right now. I know it's... a lot. I, uh--
I should have listened.
I just want to go home...
but home doesn't even feel like home anymore...
You ruined it.
You need to understand... your mother and I...
I just-... I felt-... She's always been...
I haven't been- Ha-... We weren't in...
I'm sorry, I- I- I don't have the words.
Are you gonna run off with him?
And leave me behind?
Go away where...
I can't find you?
What? No! No, no, never.
I'd never do that. Never.
I think it's time to leave this place.
You were right. You are too old for it, anyway.
So, what would you like to do now?
Oh, can we go to Stylish Occult?
They sell weird taxidermy there.
Hmmm, okayyyyy...
Thanks, dad.
You're okay sometimes.
Thank you, Via. Thank you.
Way to ruin another good thing, sir!
Worth it! That slutty toy clown had. It. Comin'!