[MOANS]
I’m sorry for having to move our little rendezvous early.
I have an engagement this month on the full moon.
When this happens, it’s not
really something I fuss about...
But do you really need the book
for this farm bullshit?
I have, like, fifteen new clients
waitin' for heads to roll.
As shocking as it may seem, Blitzy,
my grimoiiiiiire is actually incredibly important.
And it isn’t supposed to be lent out
to itty-bitty Imps like yourself.
The Harvest Moon is a very special occasion!
It’s been my annual duty to showcase it in the Ring of Wrath.
It’s celebrated by a very charming little festival with the locals.
Wrath, huh?
My employees are from there.
I’ve never really there,
It's full of inbred chucklefucks.
Oh! Why don't you all join me
at the festival?
I can guarantee you all special access~.
[GIGGLES]
Look, I told you we're not bodyguards, okay?
That was a one-time thing we did badly.
I'm simply offering a work-free day of fun!
I feel quite safe at the Harvest Festival.
It's the same every year.
Well, if you promise this isn't some fuck fest invite.
It does sound like it could be a blast and a half.
Plus, it's not like we can do jack shit without your book anyway.
Aww, I’m sowwy your clients will have to wait…
Oh, fuck my clients!
[SNORES]
[LOUD RINGTONE]
What do you want, sir?
Hey, hope I didn't wake ya, Mox!
How would you and Mils like to visit
the Wrath Ring for some harvest bullshit this year?
The Harvest Moon Festival?!
Yee-fuckin'-haw!
Well, Millie likes the idea.
Wait...
Where are you calling from?
Mhm...
Of course.
Momma!
Daddy!
Yeehaww!
How's my deadly little pumpkin spice doin'?
I’m good, Pa!
Thanks for lettin' us stay here
for the harvest jamboree.
It's no trouble.
We know you aren't making as much anymore
since y'all went "freelance".
Freelance pays fine, Ma!
We’re doin' fiiine!
It's fine.
Anyway, y'all remember my husband Moxxie?
Huh.
Greetings, Lin! Joe!
How have you been now with all the flaming
twisters and stuff around here?
We lost our old farm head to one of them terrors last week.
[NERVOUS LAUGH]
Oh... Oh, crumbs.
My bad!
I am so sorry.
I didn't mean to open that wound, sir.
Hey! Watch it. I'm the "sir" here, bucko!
Oh yeah!
Y'all haven't met my boss Blitzø
and his hellhound!
I'm not just his hellhound.
Yeah! She's my daughter!
Only on paper.
Y'all don't deserve to know my name.
It's a pleasure to finally meet the
sperm and egg factory that popped out this
little gen of an assassin.
You two raised a study bitch!
That we do!
So... Blitzø is it? Heheh
That's a fine name.
It reminds me of war.
[sighs happily]
Nothing like a little war to make a strong man!
I like you people.
Y'know...
More battles were won by
technological advances in warfare.
I've researched the history of weaponry extensively
and it's inspiring how...
for example, the progression of guns utilizing
angelic technology has changed
the landscape of Hell’s combative…
I mean…
War fun!
Guns get the job done, but a man ain't nothing
if he can't tear the head off a hellish beast
with only his bare hands!
[LAUGHS]
He's right, Moxxie!
You got cute wittle baby hands
like your baby dick.
Refrain, sir.
Speaking of strong hands!
Y'all should meet our newest help!
Hey, Striker!
Well, howdy!
Oh, looky here!
You must be the famous Mildred.
Heard some good things
about you from your folks, little lady.
Ohhh!
What're y’all doin' so far away from Imp City?
Heh. The free workin' finally slowin' down?
Oh no! Freelance isn’t free!
It's a--... Never mind.
We’re just visitin' for the festival.
The prince is our boss’ boyyyyfrieeeend!
Millie, I am not above hitting a female in front of her daddy.
Boss, huh...?
Ohhh, so YOU'RE the bold imp to start his own killing biz?
Yeah, well if you’re good at somethin',
you should probably capitalize.
Not many Imps start businesses on their own.
That’s pretty impressive, sir.
Oh...!
Yeah? It is-- I- I- I guess- I guess it is, isn't it?
So you even conned that ditzy
blueblood into gettin' you to the surface?
Well, it’s long and complicated,
but the short answer is yes.
But he’s not like, you know--
W- We’re y- We're not, like... We’re not doing it...
We w- What's betw- It’s a transactional fucking, you see.
Y'know... you boys should enter the Pain Games!
I heard games! What games? I’m in!
Every harvest festival,
there’s a competition to be the roughest,
toughest bastard in Wrath!
Yeah! Wish I could play!
Millie, you know you get too carried away.
The last competition ended in fifteen separate funerals.
I’m aware, but I only caused nine of them!
How come Sallie May still gets to compete?
Your sister doesn’t have a neighborhood head count.
She so does!
It doesn't count if they don't find the bodyyyyyy!
Still, you get to root for her and your brothers,
and now you can cheer on your boss!
Y'know, she can also cheer for me.
[LAUGHS]
...Wait, you?
Yeah! I can compete, can’t I?
Sorry, boy, but I don’t think sensitive,
thespian types would last very long in the games.
I was born here, too!
I have some fight in me!
Huh. Well then, little fella...
Why don'tcha help me wrangle one o' them hogs for dinner?
Simple. Watch me!
Nah... with these.
Bullets can’t pierce the shell.
You gotta get the knife underneath and
pry yourself an openin'.
Oh! Right, right. I knew that.
Now, just remember, your rep with the in-laws
is on the line here!
So, no pressure at all, you totally will
not make an ass of yourself in front of everyone important in your life.
Go get 'em, tiger.
Ohhh.
Mox, you don’t need to do this!
Oh, he totally does.
KICK ITS ASS, MOXXIE!
YEAAAAAAAAAAAH!!
FUCK yeah, Moxxie!
Ride it, Moxxie!
Make it that bitch you won’t call back in the morning!
This is fucking beautiful.
Doin' great, Moxxie!
Send me that video later.
Ow... My clavicle!
Don’t worry, little one...
You never stood a chance.
Hey, boss man!
You wanna help the men skin this thing for dinner?
Oh, I am always down to skin
the manly meat with the manly men!
That’s what she said!
What "who said"?
Wait, what bitch is talking shit about me?!
Don’t let 'em get to you.
And hey, you don’t need my parents to respect you.
They will eventually.
No, they won’t.
What? I’m right, ain’t I?
Oh, I’mma enter in those games.
Hmm, how pissed would you be if I bet on him dyin'?
Welcome, I say-a, welcome-a...
all to Wrath-a Ring’s-a annual-a Harvest-a Moon-a...
a-Festival!
To kick things up, we have the great prince Stolas-a,
here to usher in this here Pain Games!
How kind, Wackford.
Greetings, tiny... Wrath Ring Imps!
I hereby welcome you all to another year of celebrating the spoils
of your labor that continue to feed the citizens of Hell!
I’m happy to kick off the start of these games that
will challenge the toughest Imps to show their skill in dominance.
Good luck to you all!
Especially that sexy little one there...
Yoo-hoo! Blitzy!
Ugh. Fuck me.
MOTHER FUC--!!
I say, I say, for the first year ever,
we have a tie for winner of the Harvest Moon Pain Games!
The winners are… Striker,
aaaaand my darling Blitzy!
Just say my name RIGHT! Fuckin' dick!
Alright, so he has the “physical advantage.”
I’m better at other things, like singing!
I’d like to take this opportunity to sing a quick song
I wrote just now, about me winnin'.
Oh, WHAT THE FUCK?!
♪ Sweet victory…
I smell the smell. ♪
♪ From up in
stinkin’ Heaven, ♪
♪ to the rugged rocks of
Hell, sweet victory ♪
♪ With everything I do ♪
♪ With every talent, I’m so
much more talented than you ♪
Isn’t this guy great?
♪ Everytime I tryyyy,
I push it and succeed. ♪
False!
It’s gonna be nice workin' with him.
Working with him...? WHAT?!
♪ Every first attempt of
every single deed ♪
Yeaaaah!
I asked him if he wants to join I.M.P.
You asked… But…
♪ Me! I’m totally the best. ♪
Mox, I think you’ve had enough for now.
Let’s head back to the house and get you clean.
♪ The super cool
me, handsome guy- ♪
[cough]
♪ Moxxie, go fuck yourself ♪
♪ Did you hear something?
It was just the wind. ♪
Thank you. You're too kind.
Well, that’s troubling.
Oh my crumbs!
A genuine carmine crafted blessing-tipped rifle!
How…
How in the fuck did he get one o' these?!
Why don’t you ask me, little dude?
Shit!
W- Why do you have this... mister?!
You are aware this kind of weapon can kill--
…demon royalty?
Yes. That.
No shit.
That’s kinda the point.
Okay. Well I’m-
I’m relatively concerned by your possession of this...
I’m also glad my instant dislike of you has been vali--DATED!
Pathetic.
Millie…
I’d kill y'all, but I feel like there’s more leverage
with your rodeo clown of a boss if I don’t!
Plus, you little things ain't worth the cleanup.
Millie!
Oh, Satan!
Moxxie, I’m fiiiine!
I got worse than this during the flower tufts at my brother’s weddin'.
But I caught that fuckin' bouquet,
and it was fuckin' worth it!
You just have to get out there, and
fuck up that brownnosin' cocksucker for me!
But I can’t break through it.
I’m not strong enough.
Not with your hands, baby.
Use what you’re good at.
I’m not good with my hands?
Ohhhh.
Right. Yeah. Yeah.
I… I probably should’ve used this earlier, huh?
I love you hun…
but for fuck’s sake!
My dear commoners of the Ring of Wrath!
I, Stolas of the Ars Goetia, hereby curse this year’s
harvest with the glow of the true Harvest Moon!
Uh, excuse me?
The FUCK?!
Bliiiitzø!
I thought you were still at the ceremony!
You thought I wanted to stand around with a buncha
hillbillies excited about corn n' shit with a thirsty owl on stage?!
Huh.
And now you seem disappointed in me.
Yeaaaaah.
Well, I’m not a fan of someone I offered a job to about to off my
easiest lengthy ticket to Earth behind my back.
Blitzø, come on.
You know, the two of us are superior than most of our kind.
And you were so above suckin' on a disgusting, rich,
pompous Goetia, only to sneak topside for scraps and
work for bitter sinners, who could care
less who you are, when you could be slaying Overlords.
Why struggle to run a business that is rigged against you?
When you could partner up with me and kill...
the unkillable?
Starting with the one that treats you like a plaything?
Ooh, that’s kinda hot.
We could be the most dangerous beings in Hell, Blitzø.
Wow. That was a good fuckin' pitch.
Been workshoppin' it.
Y'know what? Fuck it. I’m in.
Huh?
Took ya long enough, Mox!
Ha-HA! Wow, you should’ve seen your dipshit face!
Wow...
Woah, okay. Cliché much?
Oh, you daddy fucker!
AAAAGH!!
AAAGH!
You dumb fucks lost the upper hand fast, huh?
HA! You seem to have forgotten something, fucko!
[WHISTLES]
Ugh, fuckin' damn it, Loona.
It’s a damn shame, Blitzø.
We might actually've made a good team...
Ah well.
In your wet dreams, you honky-tonk GOAAAAT!
I still think it’s embarrassing.
You’re wastin' a lot of potential relyin' on a weak little--
You gonna finish that fucking sentence...
pard'ner?
Vermin.
Who’s weak now, BITCH--?!
'Kay, I’m here.
Maybe you’ll get me next time... Blitzy.
I can’t believe you let him trap you, Millie!
Haven’t we taught you better?
I was seein' red, Ma!
And he was slippery!
Excuses! You’re better than that, Mildred!
Y'know, she protected me.
And maybe I’m not a strong beefy dickhead,
but Millie has the strength enough for both of us!
You two are getting on her case about being hurt by a psychopath you hired?!
Shaaaaame on you!
Aw, Moxxie, look at you!
Speechin' like a big boy with his big paaaants!
Wooow! He nodded!
He’s never acknowledged your input before!
Soooo, is that progress?
Huh...
I failed to kill the target at the festival.
But don’t worry, ma'am...
It won’t happen again.
It better not!
I want this cheating prick dead!
I don’t care who you have to go through!
MAKE IT HAPPEN!!
Understood.
I’ll get him next time.
♪ Sweet Victory ♪
♪ With everything I do ♪
♪ With every talent, I’m so
much more talented than you ♪
♪ Everytime I tryyyy,
I push it and succeed. ♪
♪ Me! I’m totally the best. ♪
♪ The super cool
me, handsome guy- ♪
[cough]
♪ Moxxie, go fuck yourself ♪