My birthday, my birthday!
It's my birthday!
Yay! Birthday, birthday!
Woohoo!
Birthday time!
Calm yourself, young prince.
You know excitement is unbecoming of a Goetia.
Oh, right.
But father told me today's the day
I am old enough to know my
purpose and responsibility.
Of course, I'm sure it will be wonderful.
Ah, there is my little, uh...
Which son is this one?
There's so fucking many.
Stolas, your highness.
Stolas! Yes!
Ha! Right!
Right! Heheh! That's the one!
The owl boy.
Well, my little one.
It is finally your day of becoming
a true part of the Goetia family.
How good for you.
Are you ready to know what you'll
be meant to do to serve Hell?
Yes, father!
You will be entrusted with the
study of the Earth's skies.
The stars, the prophecies they hold.
All that stuff.
Ain't that fun?
You will begin the studies of your grimoire,
which will grant you access to the mortal realm
to study and observe and you will grow
to be a mighty prince of Hell
with your allegiance to lead and
pass on your knowledge to.
I will do my best, father!
Wonderful!
Also, son, you were destined to sire.
Precautionary addition to the Goisha family,
so, you are now engaged.
Congratulations, isn't she charming?
Oh! That's an ugly noise, son.
Here, how about you cease this bitch crying.
Huh, that usually works.
Or would you like it if I took
you to the circus in town?
Children enjoy the circus.
Right?
Would that distract you enough from
your non-negotiable future marriage?
Is there a spot that's close to the front
but also far enough that I don't have to...
Oh, smell the poor?
Oh, ho ho ho ho ho.
Oh, ho ho ho.
Ho ho, ho ho.
Oh, ho ho ho ho.
Now, everyone's favorite thing about circus shit!
The motherfucking clowns!
Ready, Blitzo?
Born ready.
Heya, folks!
Wanna see me make a horse?
Crap!
[Nervously sings]
Uh, heh heh.
Horns!
Well, heh, it was a horse.
But then it ate too much sugar
and its legs stopped working.
So they had to amputate.
Now, it's a gross worm horse.
See? He gets it.
'Cause horses, they make no sense.
Okay, Blitzo.
That's enough horsing around.
Hey, everybody! Look at this!
It's Banana Pudding the Clown Horsey!
Neigh!
I liked his broken horse joke.
It was funny!
Their legs do stop working when
they eat too much sugar.
It's called Laminitis.
What a show! Haha!
That was real great.
So, uhem, that little clown you have.
My son really enjoyed that one.
I was wondering if I could buy him?
Buy him?
Purchase him.
Yes. Accurate.
My son doesn't have any friends, you see.
And he liked the little clown boy.
It's his birthday.
He's so sad and I don't want to deal with him.
Can I write a check?
Well, Fizzarolli is a big draw.
He has a few more shows to be in today, so
he would be pretty expensive.
No no, the other one.
Blitzo?
Correct!
How much?
Well, he's my son, so ba hm.
Ah, how much do you have in your pocket?
A... uh
A wadded-up five and a slim fit condom.
Ah.
That's plenty.
Done.
Splendid!
Fetch him for me and we'll be on our way.
I am Banana Pudding and I like to dance!
I am Worm Horse,
and I...
I am sad.
Why are you sad, Worm Horse?
Because!
I have no legs!
Oh.
Well, that's okay.
I lost my legs in the war!
The war!
Yes!
The great pirate war.
No!
No pirates!
It's a great pirate war!
If you keep talking about pirates, I will punch you.
I fought bravely, but I can never run fast enough.
They took my legs.
There was blood everywhere.
Oh, no! Ew!
No blood!
Blood is disgusting.
No! It's cool!
Well, Banana Pudding is here to save the day!
With his magical feet he dances around with,
he will dance all over Worm Horse
and make him feel better.
And then...
There'll be more blood!
Blitzo! That's so gross!
Stop!
Never!
Boy, I got a job for you.
You are gonna spend the day with one of the Goisha princes.
Ew. Why?
Because money!
Now, listen carefully!
You are being bought out to be his playmate.
But I want you to steal as much from those rich fuckers
as you possibly can.
Steal?
But...
What if I get caught?
Don't you want your family to
be able to buy a bigger tent?
Better food?
Don't you want to be able to help me and your momma out?
Of course I wanna help momma!
Then you gotta do this.
Everything those rich fucks have will be worth a fortune!
But if I'm caught...
I'm scared, Dad.
There are scarier things.
Aren't there, son?
But...
Yes, Papa.
Here is a new friend, my son.
Happy birthday.
A friend?!
I guess.
Hi. Uh...
I'm Blitzo.
I'm Stolas. It's nice- Ouch!
Don't bow to that one!
He bows to us, idiot.
Oh, right.
Sorry, Father.
I'm so good at daddying.
Ugh...
This is my book on the difference between foxes and toads!
There's a lot of differences.
And this is my book on plants and herbs!
Did you know plants can hear you?
Plants are boring.
This is all boring stuff!
Oh...
I'm sorry.
I've never had a friend to share my books with.
You know what would be fun?
A game!
Let's play Treasure Hunt.
What's that?
It's where we pretend to be pirates
and we go around the house collecting all the nicest things!
And then we throw them out the window!
We...
throw them out the window?
Yes.
Since when did pirates throw things out windows?
Since like, the dawn of time.
Come on, pirates are always throwing stuff out windows.
I... don't think they had windows.
What, did a book say that?
Yes, actually. Several.
Well, in this game we're throwing them out the window
because it's fun!
Well, that's an odd game.
Is this an Imp game?
Suureee.
Why not?
Well, if it's what you want to play.
Let's do it!
Come on, come on, come on!
Ooo, woah!
Ooo, yes!
Yay!
Woo, yeah!
Blitzo!
Over here!
So, what is that?
Your diary?
No!
This is my new grimoire!
It's a spell book!
I have to learn it so that I can access the living world!
The living world?
Like, the one with humans and stuff?
Where the sinners come from?
Mhm!
That's cool!
Yes!
I'm supposed to learn to use it,
to study the sky!
Why?
My dad says I can find prophecies.
But, I don't really know.
But I'm supposed to.
That's what my job will be when I grow up!
To join the rest of the Goetia family.
Well, you know what I'm gonna do when I grow up?
I'm gonna run my own circus!
And I'm gonna be the most famous Imp ever!
And I'll be able to do what I want to do!
All day!
I'm gonna make so much money
and buy myself a big building with a big office!
A big office?
For a circus?
Yeah! A big office!
Circus business with clowns and horses!
And the horses will all have good names!
Like Stapler and Biscuit Queen!
I'm sure you will.
That sounds like a good business.
Yeah! And if you apply, I'll hire you!
Maybe.
Ha ha ha!
You'll hire me?
Yeah, if I feel like it.
Well, I hope I qualify!
You'd be a good boss.
You say that with sarcasm but...
I totes would.
Ugh...
I know. Still being married isn't a big enough occasion but to be fair...
It's no picnic being married to a boring stiff like Stolas.
Stella, what in Hell is this?
Ugh, Stolas. You know I like throwing parties.
Plus, it's true so...
You can come if you want.
No!
Stolas is terrible in bed!
I swear to fuck he just lays there staring at the wall
and I have to do everything.
It's embarrassing.
I'm glad one egg fell out of me
so I could stop pretending to want to fuck his scrawny twig arse.
What a pathetic, fucking man.
Do you have anything stronger than this?
We have absinthe, your highness.
Bring me all of it.
Poor people!
Ugh, I'm so glad that they're not allowed into this thing.
I don't want them anywhere near me.
Can you imagine if you didn't have money?
Stolas, sir!
I'm fine.
We caught this nasty Imp trying to sneak into you chambers.
What should we do with him?
Into my chambers? Really?
Oh, well... that is...
concerning.
Leave him to me.
I will handle him accordingly.
Follow me, Imp.
Look, I didn't mean to interrupt your...
whatever, party, or uh...
I was just trying to-
Don't bother with excuses. I know why you are here.
You do?
Yes.
You are here to ravish me, weren't you?
Uh...
You?
Why else would you be breaking into my room?
You could have asked to visit, you know?
It's been a long time but I have a very good memory.
Oh, yeah...
Yeah, well uh... y'know, I figured...
Y'know, since you're a prince and all
it might be just easier to scale the wall and slip on in.
Certainly is easier than going through your fucking staff.
One would think you might be here for nefarious reasons
if you are sneaking in during the cover of night.
Oh, I wanted to crash the party and it's always more fun
y'know, to make an entrance.
I recall how you enjoy making an entrance.
So... over two decades since I last saw you.
Are you still a circus clown?
Oh, pfft, n-.
No, not anymore
No, I kill people now.
Oh, heheh.
How afraid should I be?
Well, I mean...
How afraid do you wanna be?
Oh! Well, uhm. Well, I, uh...
Y'know, I was teasing.
I don't really...
Now, you seem pretty tense.
How about I...
help you out there?
Eeuhhm.
Heh, y'know this is, uhm, getting a wee bit...
Is it hot? I'm starting to feel it getting very hot.
What are you doing? I barely your name!
It's Blitzø.
Oh, didn't it have an "O" at the end?
Like a clown name?
I remember...
Yeah, well it's silent now, okay?
So call me...
Blitzø.
Okay, Blitzø.
What are you doing to me?
What do you want me to do to you?
I... uh, pfft, well...
Oh, my fuck!
Wow!
Oh! You are so forward, Blitzø!
Oh! What are we doing?
Nope, no!
Stay down, dammit.
Oh? So you like to come on.
Do you like being in charge, hm?
Yeah, I sure do.
Oh, so you're a kinky little Imp, are you?
Do you like it when I talk to you dirty?
I want you to ▇▇▇▇ me with you ▇▇ ▇▇▇▇▇
and get it all the way  ▇▇▇▇.
Get it all the way through me, you ▇▇▇▇▇
No, stop it.
Yes, if that's what Blitzy wants.
Blitzy, oh my!
Yeeesssss!
Oh! I've never had anyone want me this way.
You have no idea how long I've craved this kind of passion.
And how much it means that the one who wants me is...
my first ever friend!
Ugh, alright fine.
I can do this real fast.
Sorry, I fucked your husband!
What... the fuck was that, Stolas?!
That was the sound of a
FUCKING DIVORCE!
♪Owl in a cage♪
♪You show your age♪
♪Your sweetness has run foul♪
♪Without a change
you're lost, exhausted♪
♪by your time♪
♪On stage♪
♪Then you walked in my room♪
♪And light sparks in the dark♪
♪Life was suddenly
thrilling and new♪
♪What between you and I♪
♪Just a comfortable lie♪
♪I'm the fool who believes
when you look in my eyes♪
♪Prince, all alone,
upon your throne♪
♪Your power is so frail♪
♪You raise your voice♪
♪You have no choice♪
♪Inside your gilded jail♪
The fuck are you doing?
Reflecting.
Well, stop.
It's annoying to hear you screeching your silly woes all the time.
Why are you still here?
You leave with Via on weekends,
but then you stay around the house despite everything.
I like tormenting you.
I want to keep reminding you of what you did.
I know what I did.
I would feel bad if I hurt you,
but we both know I didn't do that.
You and I were arranged for one reason;
to birth a precautionary heir to the Goetia family, nothing more.
I tried so many years to make it comfortable for us
to have this family, but it was never enough.
The only reason I have endured your constant
insults and cruelty was for that girl to have a normal life.
I cannot do this anymore.
I want you out.
Now.
What do you mean out?
I mean out!
Out of this palace, out of my life!
We are getting The Divorce!
How dare you?!
What do you think the rest of the Goetia family will think?
Andrealphus-
I don't care what your arrogant brother thinks!
And the only thing the Goetia family wanted
from our marriage is already 17,
so it's over!
I'm done!
Fine.
I have no desire to stay in the place of a traitorous embarrassment.
You have fallen from what little grace you had,
and I know you'll pay for it.