SO! Today you have a meeting with
the distributor about the new shipment of vibrators...
you have a nooner with Prince Stolas
you're pretty good at
"squeezing things in"
unless you want me to take
a crack at cooking again?
yeah, I know I can pick up
some more while I'm out today
y-you have a packed day today,
and I know you aren't big on the whole Mammon thing... So...
You know I ain't afraid of ropes
I'm s l i p p e r y
only after I...
but it's not like
I'm gonna stick around
Laughter]
you know I can't say no
to a face that cute
huh?
and keep your phone on ya, ok?
whistles]
girls!
it's great not be
in the spotlight for once!
it's not MY fault if
you only know how to make coffee that tastes like piss!
huh?
clown
ya know
sure!
bitch!
TWICE in the last fifteen years!
IN HISTORY!
well...
had a royal on the ropes
just last week...
kids...
"Blitzy"
you can never be too large
and that's good!
that's good, mhmm...
how you been?
um, that's actually what I'm here about
I um...
I can tell ya
shouldn't be about force...
and legally
Stolas...
but my partner
Fizzarolli
right?
but trust me
sorry...
you will give me exactly what I want
I know
jester
it's like
you've never been tied up before
sure by not by a buncha psychos
that checks
I'm sure your big royal chicken
ain't gonna let anything happen to his peppy lil' fuck doll
I fuck who I want when I want
the way princey was cozying up to you at Ozzie's
ya know...
I don't actually care
Stolas is just a loud, thirsty, bitch who
loves feeling the thrill of getting dicked by the lower class
and comment on my photos and...
RIGHT?
and I mean NO ONE,
pretends to care that much just for a cheap lay
I guess you're right
asshole!
great! The fucking supremacist
is on my side, wonderful....
then you're no better than any royal...
clown...
not fuck em'
can we move this along?
you need to know the contents of
this contract, you can't just sign it
I'm a fast reader
giving him permission to use
Fizzarolli's head for a wall decoration...
WHAT?!
NOT an escape arti...
BINGO!
genius?
I could stretch down there...
no...
this usually works!
this useless in combat?
I dance,
I promote products that I don't actually use..
but that'd imply I give a shit what you think
after what you DID TO ME?
it was an accident!
because people liked me better!
because you were jealous!
I thought
you were my best friend...
it was all my fault, ok?
I was.. I was TRYING
Fizz
Fizz....
and I...I KNOW I can never make that right
Fizz
HERE!
so!
specifically located in the Greed Ring...
you're telling me
getting BLOWN UP didn't ruin your life?
and you know
STILL
that's lovely.. You got
a good thing going on with that horny rooster fucker don'tcha?
it been...
CUZ YOU KNOW
ya know what I mean?
its HUGE-
I get it!
Fizz
cowboy
Blitzø
i'm gon' break you like a FUCKIN' HORSE!
yeah? Why?
I need to get up
to that window there to bust us out
comin' up!
while you get a look at.... ♪
maybe it explains EVERYTHING! ♪
you'll have dollars and gold! ♪
as the story unfolds... ♪
its... its uh ♪
limoncello (Side dish, Limoncello) ♪
Soft) ♪
Firenze, Bucatini
(Luigi, Florence, Bucatini) ♪
cinghiale (Wild boar, wild boar) ♪
you're actually pretty
good at this action-hero bullshit
royal jesters first?
YOU FUCKIN' PRICK!
I stuck around
babe...
AGAIN
if they tell anyone, I'll
today I learn
that I hate going outside!
again
babe!
Oz...
ok?
by the way asked ME
as a gift for that guy you hate!
Fizz?
don't you?
meow, cuddle meow....