yes!
I believe he finally learnt that
that filthy little beast
wait, wait, wait!
Stella.
sir!
yeah, yeah, I know what
interns are, I’m not an idiot, okay?
interns work for experience, sir.
you mean for free.
I can’t argue with
free kiddo, you’re hired!
surrender yourselves!
what are we gonna do?
fuck, fuck, fuck!
Moxxie!!
they will see us!
we can either run,
hurry, hurry.
c’mon, c’mon we got it.
Blitzø.
criminals.
guys!
is this about the orphans?
the ‘o’ is...
great job.
this is about the book?
right? But since when is
attempting a crime illegal, am I right?
okay?
Stolas, who,
I didn’t force shit!
Satan?
remember to take deeeep breaths.
yeah.
your honor,
beloved Stolas-
wait,
wait, wait, wait.
anyway?
then
he should be here, no?
Vasago.
(I will NOT shut up,)
might I also add...
that.
I am an assassin, okay?
that’s not what I meant, okay?
guys.
but he’s a lot of
fun and I think we should hear him out.
you two.
heh.
Levy?
you wanna fucking go, Mam!?
suck a dick!
this is what happens
Blitzo, and your crew,
are hereby sentenced
Levy! After we
celebrate this imps death,
huh?
what do you reckon?
Your Highness!
it was all me, okay?
Satan!
sorry.
today is an amethyst
and you’re acting kind of ruby. Yeah?
all that Hell is gonna see
not them!
what are you doing?
I did not see that coming, look
I’m sorry Mox, I did everything I could-
right?
please!
stop.
I can’t let you.
red bitch never
planned on hearing us out.
Millie.
Stolas!
baby!
(Sing it, baby!)
♪
could concoct
such a plot so sublime? ♪
you ask? ♪
♪
isn’t that adorable.
th-
you- you can’t! You can’t do this!
do something!
let me back in!
this is a sturdy door!
sir-
’course not.
ooh.
no.
ahem,
time for lunch!
urgh-
Stolas!
fuck-o!
it’s fine, Blitzø.
come with me, alright?
let’s not do that again.
thank you.
heh, ’kay? Thank you.
um.
dad.
here we go.
Blitzø.
Stolas.
Stolas I-