Mister!
it’s morning.
yeah.
I haven’t seen
you guys in a while, heh!
I say, I say.
the numbers,
I can’t make them add up!
baby.
and used it to buy THESE!
but...
we’re gonna
be evicted, we’re going BANKRUPT!
all
my hard work gone in a flash!
I have objectively correct opinions.
I need my piss bucket NOW.
ooh, okay. I am getting
a real sexy energy from this room!
there is definitely
a fuckable spirit here.
bitch.
what are you doing?
Millie.
I’m gonna sell 'em next year
the best
way to deal with being sad-
Millie.
Blitzø.
my psychic told me
I’d be going somewhere bad on Wednesday.
I didn’t think it was
mhm, interesting.
and-
no. Fast forward to who killed you.
m'okay.
okay.
lady!
hunt?
calm down!
starting with its hotness and tightness.
see
what passes on Earth for creepy,
he’s a little-
BANKRUPTCY, BANKRUPTCY!
grandma.
interesting.
yeah, this place is gonna
be ripe with fuckable spirits.
look.
come back to reality.
right?
those
ghosts aren’t gonna fuck themselves.
you Hollywood assholes
are pushy little pricks.
idiot.
but you’re getting close.
I am glad to see you folks.
except
ghosts are real, camera man.
Bethany.
then what do I
plan on fucking tonight, camera man?
real or not, this
shit needs to stop.
then we’ll
need those keys, cocksucker.
keys and condoms, hand 'em over.
I just can’t tell you how
glad I’ll be to be rid of them.
now I’m stuck with this.
we have a job to do.
just ‘cause you’re a hick
shut your bigot
mouth, I’m gettin' a reading.
there might
be someone in there!
about to get a
mouthful of si... si...
SOMETHING SEXUAL!
Delores!
Blitzø, they aren’t ghosts!
huh?
bitch!
he’s a patriot!
little shit!
I mean Humie I mean…
♪
but I’m fucking angry!
run, run, run, run. ♪
run, run, run
into the arms of ♪
♪
nice one, Mils.
so let’s get up there and-
ass!
and I-
It’s ghost-fuckers.
I always love
to have fun with you,
if that’s what you need to do,
who needs you anyway?
uh, ahh!
shit shit shit.
Satan, Satan.
Oh, FUCK!
Millie!!
oh fuck me, the hell is that?
Blitzø!
NO, NO MOM I’M SORRY!
no, don’t touch me!
everyo- I-
you came to the
wrong fucking BAR!
I work for myself, lady.
asshole.
hmm?
your new coworker.
you- you’ll fucking hate him.
what is this?
‘kay?
right?
new clients, new ring.
check it out!
not nice enough for you?
Blitzø.
all I’m good for.
but here?
fuck you.
I have spent too much
of my time, energy, and holes
okay?
smarter,
and Moxxie’s...
right?
so stop killing my buzz, and
come on, I wanna show you my office!
too.
a husband, a future.
never.
Blitzø.
it’s something that
like an infestor demon would do-
have you?
this is fun!
Mils!
bitch!
asshole.
you’re
just the muscle remember?
bitch, I see everything.
every opinion, and boy-
STOP!
combover.
buttercup!
good work Mils.
IT’S ME!
sorry!
boss.
Bethany!
fuck hotels.
huh?
you gonna keep
stalking us all the time?
your husband
is still a little fuckable.
he is.
I’m gonna do it!
my body aches! ♪
give me a try! ♪
the spectrometer’s going crazy!
we’re ghost fuckers ♪
♪
I’m ready! ♪
I wanna fuck a- ♪
wanna fuck a- ♪
I totally regret it.
she fucked a ghost. ♪