You know, I checked the scale today.
And it said I lost two pounds this week.
I. Am not. FAT!
Millie, honey. Everything okay?
Yeah. Just, bumped into an ex.
Oh! Oh...
He just kept going on about how he has money now,
and "a bright future," and "a bigger cock."
Wait, what?
Every time I see his stupid face, I can't help it!
I just need to--
What the fuck is all this noise?!
I got a client!
Sorry, sir. I'll get this all cleaned--
what is this?
Uh... research!
For science!
Just put it back correctly, okay, I alphabetized them.
Okay, so let me get this straight:
you don't want us going to Earth at all for this job?
Correct. That will not be necessary.
I'd like to meet you and your whole crew at my estate.
Uh, you want us killing someone in hell,
'cause I gotta tell ya, that ain't exactly our business no more.
I'll tell ya all about it when you're here.
It's in regards to a business venture I'm sure will be very worth your time.
Ooh, how ominous.
Fine, whatever, what's the address?
Transportation has already been taken care of.
What the fuck is that?
Satan's ass crack!
Enough with the walls, shit, we have a door!
My research!!
I.M.P.? Right this way, please!
Uh, sir? What's going on?
Now, don't worry!
It's just some fancy shmuck from Greed wanting to do business with us.
Uh, sir, I don't think this is a good idea.
It'll be fine. Now get your asses moving.
Is this thing safe?!
Don't worry, we are professionals!
Ugh, I hate this place.
Oh yeah, this is your old stomping ground, isn't it, Mox?
Yeah, unfortunately.
I grew up just over there, swore I'd never come back, and--
uh... uh-- what-- what, where are we going?
What-- Blitzø...
who did you say this meeting was with?
I'm not sure, just some rich somebody
or other who wants to do biz at his place.
Oh no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, NO!
There he is!
There's my boy!
Get over here and give your daddy a hug!
Daddy?!
I only let Moxxie call me that...
unless you pay me!
Guys, this is my father, Crimson.
Sir, this is my boss, Blitzø. And my--
Millie!
I'm his wife!
And what a beautiful wife you are.
Mox, where have you been hiding this pretty little thang?
Oh, I'm sure he would've introduced us... eventually.
Oh, I'm sure.
You gotta be Blitzø, with the silent "o", right?
I've heard a lot of good things about you and your work.
Really? What kind of shit has Moxxie been spreading about me?
I'll fucking kill you Moxxie, don't you fucking test me!
No, no! From all over.
Looks like you're building a bit of a name for yourself here, kid.
Really?
Ha!
Well, I guess it's about time folks recognized my talent.
I like your attitude.
Well, I hope you're all hungry.
We put together a fabulous dinner for you.
Hey baby, why haven't I met your Pa before?
Well uh, y'know, i-it's just, never been a--
Hey! You two, move it before it gets cold.
Look, look, Millie, we can talk about it later.
So, Blitzø, ya always been a hitman?
No, no, not always.
I was in the circus for a long time.
Show business!
Good money in that.
What are we doing here, sir?
Moxxie, I raised you better than that.
Ya know there's no business before dinner.
Besides, we're still waitin' on one more.
Woo-hoo-hoo, what is up, party people?!
Chaz?! Wait... What?!
You know him?!
Ugh! You remember that "ex" I was talking about?
Looks like I got two big sex reunions today.
How lucky am I?!
Did you date him too?!
Ha, yeah.
No big deal, but I usually bone half the people in any room I'm in--
Are you fucking kidding me?!
There's someone who's fucked both of you?!
It was a long time ago.
But I still remember it like it was yesterday.
You, a fledgling mafioso!
Me, the dashing and extremely sexy muscle!
It was like it was written in the stars.
Ha! Moxxie in the mafia, that's fucking rich.
Oh shit.
You've never told me this before.
I don't like to talk about this part of my life.
But, I first saw Chaz at my induction...
...in the family.
Our eyes met from across the room.
And there was just something about him...
something that was... magnetic!
It's been 84 years...
Isn't that from that "boat" movie?
Did any of that stuff actually happen?
Oh yeah!
But he skipped over the jizz-covered parts.
Anyway. Things changed when we went on a heist together.
So what're you in for?
Okay, not much of a talker, are we?
I'm Blitzø, the "o" is silent.
I'm sure we're gonna get along just fine.
So, what's your deal?
What'd you do?
Who'd you diddle?
You look like someone who's good with a gun.
You look like someone who could shoot up an office
and I hope you are 'cuz I got a plan to get us out of this dump
but I'm gonna need some help,
you think you can give me a hand?
I need to get out to my daughter.
The babysitter will kill me if I don't get back soon...
Once I got out, I never looked back.
Well, heh, like you said, it was a long time ago.
I'LL FUCKING KILL YOU!!!!
Whoa, the fuck!
Crazy bitch.
Hey, hey hey, hey hey!
Hey, hey hold on!
You're gonna die, bitch!
Dinner is served.
So, this is aggressively uncomfortable.
I suppose you wanna know why you're here.
Yeah, so what gives?
You know we kill people on Earth, right?
We don't normally do contracts for locals so,
if you wanna do business with us, you gotta-
I don't wanna do business with I.M.P,
I wanna do business with Moxxie.
ME?!
Yeah, kid. I summoned I.M.P to be sure you'd show.
Because, well, we're bringin' Chaz into the family.
What?
Since when can just anyone join the family?
Come on, Mox.
You had responsibilities here that I had to pick up once you left.
Now Chaz is going to lighten the load.
Wait, thought you always hated his guts.
Well, I don't that I exactly 'hated' him.
You called him a "friendless horse-fucker"
and said we lived a "sissy lifestyle".
Yeah, well I was wrong.
You've been gone a long time, Mox.
A man can change.
And so has Chaz.
Yeah. I've grown, matured and, recently, came into millions!
But, y'know, mostly the "mature" thing.
Ohh okay, okay.
So the "horseless friend-fucker" over here gets a little moolah
and suddenly, it's worth wasting our time over?
Well, I'm the whole "package" if you know what I mean.
I got a big dick.
But what does any of this hafta do with Moxxie?
There's gonna be a ceremony tomorrow.
Moxxie here is going to officially release his holdings in the organization.
Then you can get back to ignoring your family to your hearts content.
Maybe he wouldn't "ignore his family"
if they didn't force him to rub elbows with a no-good,
shark-toothed FUCK FACE!
Ey, look, everybody relax.
I know tensions have been high tonight.
Say, why don't you stay here and get some rest.
We'll have the ceremony tomorrow and then you will be free to leave.
I have your rooms all prepared.
Yes sir.
Mox?
A moment, Moxxie.
Just give me a minute, Millie.
I'll be there.
So.
You think you're too good for this family now?
What?
C'mere.
I--...
I don't understand.
You think you're gonna just get to
walk away from this family
and never come back?
You're dead wrong, Mox!
Matter of fact, the only thing you're
right about...
is that obnoxious piss-stain can't get made.
Not unless he marries in!
Marries?
But, but who would he--?
Who do you think?
This family needs that money and it's about time
your pathetic ass was useful for something!
Sir, I'm already married.
I-I can't-
You think I give a shit about your stupid beard?
C'mon Mox, I even went through the trouble
of makin' the house more to your kind's liking.
Wait What?
What do you think I'm into?
What? This is the kind of shit gays like, right?
First off, Dad. I'm bisexual.
Yeah. Gay.
Oh, for fuck sake!
Secondly,
I don't know a single person of any sexuality who would enjoy this.
Ha! There's dicks on the walls!
Oh, that's fucking hilarious!
Look at me, kid.
One way or another, you're going to do what I fucking say.
Don't cross me.
Let this be a lesson, Moxxie.
This is what happens when you cross me.
Now get to bed Moxxie.
You have a big day tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Oh, and Mox,
if you ever talk back to me again,
you and that pretty little thing you brought
here are goin' home in boxes.
Capeesh?
Yes, sir.
Wait how comes we aren't in-
Crimson wants you all to stay in separate rooms.
Why? Moxxie?
It's just one night Millie, it's ok.
Mox are you ok?
I'm fine please don't worry sweetie.
You know you can tell me anything, right?
Yes. Everything's fine.
We're partners, Mox.
It's just my dad, it's OK really.
It'll be over tomorrow.
Ok, I love you.
I love you too.
Goodnight.
What the--?
Fucking why?
Like what I've done with the place?
Ugh. Just get out of here!
Come on, Mox.
We used to have so much fun here.
Remember?
I'm married, Chaz,
and even if I weren't I would never.
Never what? Let me take you to cum town again?
You are so gross!
Just leave me alone!
I know what you want most Moxxie Poxxie.
How about a sexually charged musical number.
HEY! You always loved those.
Wow!
Wo-oa-oh.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's Chaz time.
Moxxie, I see you looking at me looking at you
wondering when I'm going to crack you open
like a walnut and the answer is soon.
Now I'm feeling how you're feeling
and I'm feeling that you want to
feel my feelings... and f--...
the feelings. You feel me?
Saxophone.
Yeah... So let me get a little something off my chest
while I blow off a hot and emotional load onto yo' face.
Moxxie, feeling foxy, Want to give me a good taste of your boxxy?
And I've got two tickets to pleasure land.
Oh baby!
And I'm now here to have your way hey yeah, yeah,
with my sexual bod-ay-ay yeah, yeah!
So long yeah!
Moxxie?
What do you want?
Wow!
Woah, woa--
Damnit, this usually works.
Hey there good looking.
Oh, I was wondering how long it would take you to make a pass.
Mm, does that mean you're down to clown?
Ew. what the.
You think I would violate my friend's trust by sleeping with their ex,
especially one who fucked them over the way you did?
I'll show you all of the things they liked in the sack.
Deal.
Chill the fuck out!
Ok, fucker, nobody who's that bad in bed can score two hotties that easily,
I know you gotta be hiding something.
Oh fuck that!
No one fucks with M&M's marriage but me!
Sorry, babe, you're not the only junk in my trunk!
Damnit, that was not a good one!
Hey, hey! The man of the hour. You ready to get started?
Wait, where's Blitzø?
I think I saw him head outside he said something about
needing some fresh air.
Or something.
Why don't you grab him so we can get moving?
Be right back, baby.
What ya looking so glum for kid,
it's your wedding day, the best day of ya life.
I'm not doing it.
What was that?
I couldn't make it out over the sound of you being a whiny bitch!
I said I'm not doing it, sir.
I've spent my whole life being afraid of you,
but I'm not giving up the only good thing I've ever had
just so you can keep your fragile little sense of control over everything.
Millie is a good woman, a better woman than I deserve,
and there's nothing that scares me more than hurting her.
Not even you.
I'm leaving, Dad, and if you or Herpes the Clown are over here--
Hey!
Try and stop me you'll learn firsthand just how good I've gotten at my job.
Now take care of the others.
Oh, Millie, you found me.
Who's your friend?
Friend?
Is everyone here?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, don't worry about it,
let's get this thing rolling, ey?
Mmmph!
Awww, you told me all the chairs would be filled!
Satisfied?
Oh, fuck yes.
What is going on?
That seductive dick-hole is trying to marry Moxxie,
and he's not even rich!
Moxxie!
Do you, Chazwick Thurman,
take Moxxie Nolastname to be your lawfully wedded husband?
Oh, yeah.
And do you, Moxxie, whatever,
take Chazwick Thurman to be your lawfully wedded...?
Look at that!
He's just so fucking happy to be here!
Everything's locked down!
How are we gonna get in?
Loo Loo Land, Loo Loo Land...
Buckle up, Millie...
we're doing a Shrek!
I object!
You want my husband, you're going to have to fucking kill me!
♪Oh, I ain't a stranger
to your thorns♪
♪Think I'm a damsel,
now you get the horns♪
♪Lay low my dear,
I'll get you outta here♪
♪I ain't a damsel,
I'll make that clear.♪
♪(She'll make that clear)♪
♪Just try to stop the
reckoning that's comin'♪
♪Lay down your head boy, did
you hear those beats a drummin'♪
What the FUCK?
She's a dame!
♪Be it as it may,
by death do us part♪
She's a BROAD!
Kill her!
♪Think fast cause momma's
gonna tear out your heart♪
You frigging goons!
What the fuck is the matter with you?
Why do I pay you!?
Get her!
You stupid idiots!
Go get her!
♪Giddy up, little bitch boy,
you're dead♪
Giddy up, little bitch boy,
♪You tried to take him
like you didn't know♪
♪He was mine, and taken,
now reap what you sow♪
♪You tried to take him
like you didn't know♪
♪He was mine, and taken,
now reap what you sow♪
Hey! What about my—?!
This ass is MINE!
By the way, y'all should probably know,
Chaz isn't even rich, okay?
Check his car, he just played you like a fucking rube.
Later, losers!
Ehh heh heh heh.
Millie, thank you for saving me.
You're amazing.
Next time, just tell me if your dad is a psychopath.
I can handle it.
Well, I'm glad everything ended up okay.
Good to know we both have daddy issues, Mox.
Also, I got to plow your ex-boyfriend.
Isn't that great?
Now we ALL fucked the same guy.