Prince Sleeps-A-Lot!
big bird?
I suppose.
Blitzø... hoohoo
so I don’t know what you eat,
made ‘em special!
isn’t it?
just rather off-putting.
I suppose.
nice. Anything that I
can get that’s affordable?
that’d be nice.
pick up, pick up!
please pick up.
no, no.
hey, hey, whoa! Look I’m
sure it’s gonna be okay, alright?
okay?
♪
but the pain grows ♪
and on, and on, ♪
nothing’s wrong. ♪
♪
this is how I act
when I don’t have money!
it’s Sinsmas!
the day every Hellborn
celebrates and acts on their birth sin?
whichever
ones they want, honestly!
rich people
don’t have any fun, do they?
fun is free, but we
can afford nice things.
you have to spend
your holiday at work?
last year I set my apartment on fire,
oh. Son of a bitch.
he he!
honey!!
chuckle-fucks!
sir?
Millie punch him.
happy Sinsmas, Mox.
Loony-
hello? I.M.P. - Yeah,
we can kill that asshole,
dipshit.
Blitzø.
I- I guess?
Stolas?
something to help you out,
something to do!
right?
answer it, answer it!
come on,
answer the phone!
I.M.P?
we can kill your asshole.
just bring it here.
we sure can!
lady, get it right.
well [nervous laugh]
right?
cheating isn’t really
that big of a deal anymore is it?
I don’t think this is
a job we want to take on.
that’s not-
we’ll do your shitty job,
but you’re paying us double, bitch.
♪
though
I’ll never be the same. ♪
I’m not okay today. ♪
it’s a
difficult business, I imagine.
huh?
here’s an idea!
yes, yes, yes yes!
Hello?
you fucking
suck you fucking piece of shit,
foolish fantasies!?
it is cold as shit!
babe?
let’s just hurry up and
sir.
dad?
if you’re not up for it.
fuck this.
this is fun!
Mils.
I can do this!
Moxxie!!
I know it’s Sinsmas
and it’s in the spirit of Wrath...
I don’t...
I feel lighter!
where the fuck is he?
he was just right here.
where would he go?
fucking ice queen,
how extra can you get?
Stolas.
poor thing,
BITCH!
Ha ha!
bitch!
eugh. Oh.
baby!
big weapon, stat!
cover me.
disgusting!
impressive, Moxxie!
woah shit!!!
waste of
lower class scum attack ME!
I will see aaaall
your heads mounted!
girl!
you aren’t worth
my time anyway!
I- I didn’t leave you. I-
it wasn’t my choice.
you chose him.
you don’t understand.
you love him.
please, you have always
been the only good thing in my life.
so, so much.
let me explain.
and you’ll do it again.
dad.
sure! Whatever you want, Loony.
Mmkay?
your highness?
but thank you.
♪
where’s Mils?
hey sweetie!
you alone?
okay!
for real.
how’d the call go?
too!
merry fucking
Sinsmas, am I right?
when have you ever asked?
wasn’t it?
she’ll understand eventually.
she’s gone.
my twin sister...
you know, we--
I need you to show up Russ!
I’ll be back in just a sec, ‘kay?
uh...
Blitzø.
♪
like that’s anything new.
tall horses.
♪