folks!
Give it up for the king of all things greeeen!
King of Greeeed!
implings!
Mammon, Mammon!
but first,
I do!
me, me, me, me!
I'm happy to announce that
I will be starting up a new, yearly
so it's better!
clown kids out there!
Mammon!
I mean enjoy [nervous laughter]
uh, watching me grow my empire!
if you're a chick,
maybe give up on your dreams now.
YEAH!
an action
figure, Saturday morning cartoon.
I might even make a sex robot of ya!
I don't know!
if we'll make money, sure.
But it's not weird.
you sick fuck!
fuck you!
CLOWNS!!
YEEAAA-
I'm gonna say it
Fizz.
You don't need to go work for Mammon like some
was it worth all our savings
just to have him put on an over-hyped commercial,
and then assault us
with clowns, vomit, and pass out on stage?
do you think I
could win if I worked really hard?
Fizz.
you're Fizzarolli!
Oh MAN! Your stuff is great!!
I appreciate that.
I wanted to get into clown performing, too!
that should spice up your act.
weird fuckin' pitch. Fuck off!
asshole!
I'm not normally
so aggressive, I promise.
and my raw,
undiscovered talent, I know we can-
beat it now
or I'll make ya swallow your fangs!
right?
hey don't let one asshole
get to you, 'kay?
and someday, maybe,
Mammon!
toy Fizzie,
skinny Fizzie,
you can!
fucking degenerate adults!
Fizzieee!
Mammon is gonna notice that.
Froggie.
okay?
so I- I gotta be perfect.
you ain't perfect! Nobody is!
you sit this one out,
and let someone else take the spotlight?
where you don't have to
fend off creeps the entire time.
now.
I just- have to do this!
thanks to Mammon.
a toy is a toy!
Ozz, I'm fine.
I've known that guy since the
start of Hell, and
Ozz. But this- i-is for me.
then lifelong enemy,
now newly
rekindled sort of friend, Blitzø?
that is a weird way to put it,
but eeyup, that's me.
the big Ozz himself!
Heh, is there a reason you're
big man?
he tried convincing
me that juggling was cool,
he's deadset on re-entering
Greed's yearly clown pageant.
big fucking surprise there.
manipulative, PIECE OF SHIT!
count me in!
baby, yeah!!
I have not been
to a crowd event in years.
again?
with extra security.
You know your fans.
I felt he'd be the next best thing.
babe.
Fizzarolli!
it's just like old times.
today.
there he is!
shiny,
brand baby doing?
Mammon sir.
cause, you know,
and it's pretty stiff, right?
you're looking
a bit chungo, yeah?
sir. Of course!
I'll work on that.
yes, nice to meet you,
dick show you called a performance.
by the way.
sir. He's uh-
he's like this all the time.
yeah.
boy.
okay?! [Sighs]
Fizz!
Fizz?
pfft- well,
fun.
see we didn't come to chat.
what attractive attitudes you got.
I was thinking of one!
bitch.
well. I look forward to seeing what
you do, and may the best clown-
I didn't a rat's ass about this competition,
folks.
it's objectively cool ♪
they're on fire ♪
♪
too ♪
and he's covered in goo ♪
things are not looking good
for Fizz-a-rolli ♪
uh- I may not be uh-
of course not.
come on Fizzie my boy.
[Rabid crowd noises]
mate.
Fizzie?
I mean,
not really actually.
I-I'm not gonna lie,
just do this
one thing for me.
sir.
you're a bloody legend, Fizzie!
little, [HONK].
if he talked to me that way,
it's fine.
where ya from?
love it there, obviously.
hah!
Best pharmacies in Hell!
partner.
I don't do accents. Fun!
nice to meet you, too!
you're act is such
fucking trash, always has been.
everywhere!
you can read all
about it on my review blog:
dot-com, dot-org, dot-gov.
well, anyway folks heh.
sleaze joint,
old routine.
and so do your products.
you know-
what we could've
been together if
one more word out of you twat stan
Fizzarolli.
hey- woah woah, you good?
mate? You alright Fizzie?
yeah I'm fine.
I'm- I'm fine, yeah, heh.
Fizzie.
ya bitch!
that guy got to you, didn't he?
I do.
Fizz this is stupid.
and
he's a fucking trash fire.
he's not! He's just trying
to make me good enough.
ha, here's the sitch' ♪
slutty
body to the masses ♪
bitch ♪
Fizz. You can do this.
it's fine. You have
a show to do soon, it's fine.
oh- no, no, no, no.
no-
you're fine.
You need to be fine.
Asmodeus.
please!
you're shaking.
I'm about to go on for the finale,
come on!
model performer,
Froggie.
I'm just nothing,
Mammon didn't do shit.
you know?
Ozzie.
Fizzarolli.
I kinda spent my whole warmup
haha.
crooked grin. ♪
horny, ♪
little joker. ♪
win, win. ♪
oh, oh, I think you're messy, ♪
too. ♪
no, no, I wouldn't clean a thing ♪
all I got is time.
babe. ♪
oh, ♪
♪
oh, oh
you sure are lucky ♪
little flips. ♪
BITCH.
I've won it all. ♪
♪
fuck you! ♪
Fuck you! ♪
fuckity, fuckity fuckity you! ♪
what?
♪
I've hit the wall. ♪
fuck you! ♪
just like a tumor! ♪
♪
you cuck, fuck you! ♪
say I'll never
work in this town, ♪
fuck you!) ♪
greedy bastard! ♪
ass clown! ♪
♪
last show.
I quit. I'm done,
mate!
motherfucker.
Mam.
I say.
hooo.
Ozzie.
I knew it!
Ozz.
bitch ♪
bitch Imma klown bitch, yeah) ♪
♪ Fix up your frown, bitch ♪
fix ya frown, bitch) ♪
♪ Gimme the crown, bitch ♪
bitch, gimme that) ♪
bitch ♪
bitch! ♪