come on, come on, come on, come on
now enough with this foreplay, where's Barb?
but that ain't none of your business
like I'm gonna tell you ass clown
right bitch?
she's got a job now, a life.
why don't you take that advice
and shove it right between your pussy
LIIIIIIIIIIIIIiiiiiiiiiiips
you were saying?
its just that I'm sure one of the
other camp counselors killed me
and they're the only ones who knew I couldn't swim.
we don't typically do investigations,
I'll have to check with the boss
pardon moi sir.
there's a client that needs us to
investigate his death, and we don't usually
we really need the cashflow,
and I was thinking maybe-
honey please.
Blitzø put me in charge this time
He... HE DID!
most well prepped, most surgical hit we've ever had!
did you even ask?
I'm getting another call...
Hellooooooo
did you find-
where?
and I promise if we ever get
a contract on your children
you'll find a
comprehensive guide to your cover persona
one last time for safety
the hottest,
most popular girl at my school, and you are?
I like sports
and fuckin bitches
you know these kids are a bit
younger than I was expecting
I think we're ready
Millie... I hardly think pointing out
the first guy you see is the proper way to conduct an-
and drugs, and what looks like
a drill one would use to poke holes in a boat
we just have to find the kids
with the most influence
and tried to convince us he was high
who the fuck are you?
I'm the prettiest girl at my school
puppies, fast cars, jewlery-
you wanna be frieeeeeeends?
you wish.
he is so fucking HOT!
I'm lookin for one of your employees,
her name is Barbie. Does she work here?
they're cheering,-
but Moxxine is the real deal y'all
and you're off dancing for views
go home if you want to-
I swear!
now get out there and put camp
IVANNAKUMMORE on the MAP!
and most supportive person I've ever known
you're still workin on that?
It's been like a fucking week
no call, no note-
he works for me,
and who's the little twink here?
and now our client wants to kill him back
look you're not killing my supplier
it's just heroin
sure Barb. Whatever you say
one way, or another...
Haven't you fucked my life up enough already?
you're the best ♪
I'm out of a job!
we'll catch up, and we'll talk about-
no not really.