♪
never minding. ♪
I'll remind myself ♪
♪
alright. ♪
I hate when it's complicated. ♪
getting in my head, ♪
♪
or be tough? ♪
thank you! Thank you!
ma'am.
you know
stop complaining.
didn't I?
Cletus?
Cletus.
he's sure to get into Heaven!
don't you?
then quiet your incessant winghing,
I think maybe
we can help each other out here.
Mox,
beautiful bloody mess in there.
sir.
it's the--
fuck you.
the bird started giving me more ways out
Blitzy, I know it's the Full Moon tonight,
Blitzy"
sir.
feeling like my stamina's up.
shit.
man.
tits.
I hope so, sir!
fuck him good, sir.
Mox.
grow up, Mox.
we're horny.
like, all the shit in this box.
I need you to hold down the fort.
yeah, yeah, yeah.
once we work out
yeah.
we're not even sure
that was Hell we sent them to.
with more experience.
little guys?
HA HA!!!
buddy?
if we don't do this,
but he's tall as shit.
we have some pretty long harnesses.
can't go wrong with
something that's stretches.
that is fancy.
I'm into it.
what kind of store is this?
fellow vile hellbeast!
you have come to the right place,
just your standard...
do you have any
harshly worded bumper stickers?
we have in spades.
your crops, your whips, your whisks,
sudden, un-sudden, wooden, leather, titanium, brimstone,
what are you intoooo??
earthty soul,
barbaric fashion!
thanks for doing this solid Fizz.
we have got these new beads.
Stolas never
really seamed into the beaaads.
righty, not into the beads.
really frisky,
the new
now with vibrations!
armory? War room?
darling.
NOW!!
guys, it's time.
you weren't exactly covert.
mutt!
bitch!
hon.
look at thiiis bad boy!
Blitzø?
it's right here.
no no no.
Stolas.
le-let me show you a good time tonight.
don't say it like that Blitzø!
bitch!
no, no.
is an Asmodean crystal.
you will be able to go
anywhere you want in the human realm,
you are...
fucking you good enough?
I'm giving you this because,
this transactional thing we have,
not know how they feel...
I want you, to continue to...
if you want to.
all right.
but I can get into it.
how's this, okay...
Stolas."
what?
hold on now, Stolas.
Blitzø.
Stolas!
BITCH.
Blitzø.
wait!!