you did CHEAT on the poor thing. Surely you owe...
cheating implies there was a betrayal.
this divorce is far overdue.
for fucks sake, stop making this harder to bullshit!
but um...
well no, rather unlucky
which one?
I think you should come save me.
I can't today alright? I'm sorry.
it took five to get this one.
she needs it
ha ha, well I do agree that is very important...
but I-
let me and Moxxie handle this one.
are you two sure you've got this alone?
together we are a lethal combo
well hurry.
Stolas sounds like he might be in real shit this time.
my money's that he's in Wrath.
come on
this'll be over lickity split alright?
I'm here for that S. H. O. T. for my Loonie Toonie
the B. U. L. L. SHIT that my daughter
has to get every year that you-
I don't see any Blitz on the list
yep.
Blitzoooo
we will be ready for her in just a bit.
Please take a seat Mr. "O"
It's just one little prick, you wont feel it.
don't say that, it sounds vulgar.
darn tootin, his name is Striker ♪
he's-
nice weather we're having huh?
my kids here too, and I don't
think she would appreciate you calling her father...
I bet the hardest work you've ever
done is convincing your husband that little shits his.
and what do you do that's SO important
go and see
if anyone's seen Striker anywhere.
because it was... hot...
outside...
huh?
he lives out by the bad man lands,
in the old train tunnel, near the mine shafts.
ya cant miss it.
my wife paid you for this hmm?
are you seriously judging me right now?
not every ring is some fancy ass city,
you seem to be forgetting-
and hits sooo much deeeeper
yeah, and you can hurry up please.
so lets try to
make this quick, for all of our sakes
it can't be that bad
told ya dipshit.
you. [laughs]
you know...
it wont turn out
well for you
you've already produced an heir.
his duties, his possessions,
his legions, it will all pass to...
if you kill him you would...?
you're SO lucky you're attractive...
well this kind of situation
is extremely unique.
we have options, opportunities...
Eternity is a long time my dear
and wait for the chance
to gain the upper hand.
but I want him dead so badly!
in time, my fiery vixen...
I need the prick alive.
you guys actually managed to-
sir... are you okay?
yeah no, todays been wonderful