hello, hello Stolas.
and I sent you a bunch of funny shit.
Stolas,
we just had a rough night.
you always want to hear from me.
feathered
ass out of that lawn chair
I- sh- Yeah, sure that wa- okay,
that was a shitty way for me to say it-
and fucky, and shit.
we don’t do words.
Blitzø-
I don’t think I’m even
in the mood to do words with you!
Stolas. You can’t mean that.
who the fuck’s behind this?!
it’s entirely immature.
it’s silly.
though.
it’s rather concerning you have
an entire party devoted to hating you though, Blitzø.
everyone hates
me for shitty reasons.
everyone’s just bitter
they couldn’t tie this ass down.
they couldn’t
handle that I moved on.
hm?
then bingo.
very boring.
I- waiting for you to realize how
good an angry fuck would be right now!
Stolas.
prince-y ass what a real fuckin' is.
aren’t I?
didn't I?
the- oh. Oops.
who said tha- I-
I- I stopped him!
silly me.
to support you?
but you can’t just ignore all that!
Stolas...
you think I can’t apologize?
this entire time I assumed the
worst because I was convinced a prince
yes. That.
fuck you!
everyone but you!
I know we killed you in the past,
but I just wanted to say no hard feelings,
that’s fuckin’ right.
and now onto the exes.
you know where
666 South Maple avenue might be?
demon dude!
Sick costume, bruh.
Happy Halloween!
looks like you
missed some makeup there.
what?
man, I wish I was you.
freshest ex!
you holding up okay?
I’m fine. I felt
it rude not to stop by.
but I really shouldn’t stay long.
honey.
Stolas.
you wanna slice it?
you are with friends here.
I should
start keeping count.
she’s a whore.
though I thought it was your dad.
you suck Dennis!
new guest of honor of the night,
and say a few words!
no. No, no, no. No,
I’m not really, um, heheh.
I really shouldn’t I-
speak from your heart.
ahahaha, um.
now I know,
now I know exactly ♪