In the great expanse of the nether
there exists boundless amounts of magnificent phenomenon
the great brilliance of an exploding star,
the nimble dance of space dust through a nebula
but once every one thousand years
our corner of reality is treated to an incredible sight
from the deep eldritch recesses of the cosmos
the tears of a forgotten colossus begin to fall.
Tears made of the hopes and dreams
of every living thing that never came to be.
Condensed and sent shooting
across the night sky in a dazzling final display.
What appears to mortal beings as a meteor shower
we can see for what it is: Azathoth's Tears.
Hehehe.
Daddy, can we go see it someday?
Yes, dear. I promise.
When the day comes,
nothing will be able to keep me
from being there with you.
Good night, my Owlette.
Good night!
Hey, dad!
Dad?
Yes, I know!
It will be there, shortly.
Of course they're being careful!
Dad, what's going on?
Apparently, your mother can't exist somewhere
for two minutes without the entirety of her possessions before she--
What?
No! I'm not turning her against you--
Yes, Stella!
--never have to see your fucking face again!
Dad?
Everyone-
This is going to be done before tonight, right?
What?
Oh. I hardly think so.
Knowing your mother, this will take all weekend.
Don't be gentle about it , now!
Break whatever you have to to get it all in there.
What?!
What did you just tell them to do?!
But, tonight was supposed to-
Darling, can we not talk about this now?
Your mother's being a real B-I-T-C-H.
The fuck do you mean-
Well, how was I supposed to know you can spell?!
I've never seen you read!
I'm going to take everything!
Everything you own!
Loona, honey, wait just a-- shit!
Loonie, please, can we talk--
FUCK!
Uh, I mean, wow!
A good throw, honey!
I-I'm so proud of youuuuu!
What's this all about, honey?
Ah, oh!
Blitzø finally talked to her about her attitude with clients.
I just think some small tweaks might help
you be more of a uh, people person, you know?
I am a people person!
If I'm so terrible, how about you just
grow a pair and replace me?
Okay, well, maybe I-
Maybe I might.
What?
Maybe I will, little missy!
Yeah, that's right it's tough love time.
So, now you can...
go... to your desk!
Sir, if I may say so, you're doing the right thing.
If we can't even hire a cheerful qualified receptionist,
how can people trust us to massacre and mutilate their enemies for them?
It's good for business.
Take me to see the stars.
Um, sir?
The fuck?
...Looona!
Oh, yeah. You have a visitor.
Where am I?
Oh. Woah!
Hey! This is my territory, bitch!
Take your shitty costume and get the fuck off my corner!
Shit, shit, shit, shit!
What the fuck am I supposed to tell Stolas?!
Well, he seems to like you, sir.
Maybe he would understand if --
Okay, my dick is good, but it is not that good, Moxxie.
Sir, I don't think we really have a choice.
So, what? You just want me to call him up
and be like, "Hey, Stolas" -
So, your daughter came by,
took your book, and teleported off to
"Who the fuck knows where", and we have no way
of getting either of them back, okay?!
Okay! Good talk, byeee!
Oh, that actually went better than I thought.
BLIIITZØ!
Hey, do y- Can you help -
h-how do I get ah -
I - excuse me, I just need to know where I can...
see the stars.
Yes!
How could this happen?!
Do you just let anyone waltz into your
office and grab infinitely powerful artifacts?!
Why would she do this?
How are we supposed to find her?
Where would she go?
Well, it reeks of urine and desperation so...
Ugh... L.A.
What?
Alright, Loona, let's make this quick.
In and out before anyone notices us here.
Oh. This doesn't look much different from Hell.
Alright, now let's get to work. Loonie, sniff!
How am I supposed to smell anything in this city?
Can't you even do one thing right?
Can't you finally do anything about how fat you are?
I'm not --
You know, it wouldn't kill you to put a salad
in your body every now and then.
What? But, I'm not fat!
Now, first things first we're gonna do this the old-fashioned way.
We're gonna need disguises.
No chance you can conjure us a couple of those, can ya?
Sadly, no.
I'm afraid without my grimoire,
my powers are just a tad limited in the human world.
What, you can't memorize your fucking spells?
Oh, your memory's so great?
What's his phone number?
Fuck you.
Exactly.
Hey, little man.
How about you check out this demo right here?
This is some premium Grade-A fire right here!
Perfect for you to crank with the little lady.
Oh, wow!
You made this? Thank you.
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
Hold up a sec, you just gonna grab it and go?
He said, "thank you".
20 bucks, man.
Millie, we need money to pay this talented artist!
You can just give it back, Mox.
Millie!
These artists put their heart and soul into their work!
I can't just give it back like it's worthless!
It probably is.
Sick demon costume, man!
It's metal as fuck!
I have an ide- Oh, woah!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, come back here!
I have an idea!
And to your left, you'll see the home of one
of those influencers who thinks they're
hot shit cause now they do TV shows.
So?
Look, everyone!
It's Hollywood star, Brennon Ragers!
The fuck is a Brendon Rager - Oh.
Oh, dear.
Millie, where are you and your whore bag husband?!
You're my lovely little monster, and I'll never say goodbye.
I will kill for you, until the day we die.
And, here you are, my fellow Troubadour.
Whatever, man.
Get the fuck outta here, you're cramping my business.
Come on, babe!
We have to catch up to Blitzø before -
Ayyy, wanna buy some art?
Wha? YES!
I'm taking this out of their pay!
Mr. Ragers, we've been looking for you everywhere.
You were supposed to be on set an hour ago!
The fuck are you talking about?
Your guest spot on...
"Sweetie! I'm in the House!!"
We're taping tonight.
Now, hurry up and get in the car!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm not going anywhere with you, jizz-biscuit!
Very funny, Mr. Ragers.
Now, get in the car.
Come on, boy, come on.
Get your fucking hands off me!
Loona! Stolas! A little help, here?!
E-excuse me, sir. I'm...
Mr. Ragers' agent, and I don't believe you can just--
Oh! You are strong!
Blitzø, we don't have time for this.
Via could be anywhere.
She could be in danger.
Don't worry, I'm on it.
Loonie, go find Via!
We'll catch up soon!
Yeah!
Way to be a team player, sweetie!
She's in great hands.
Let's get him ready!
He's on in five!
What?
"Five" what?
I-I can't be on a sitcom!
Should've had an ego crisis before signing the contract.
I-I-I… Whoa-,
I don't even know the fucking lines, idiot!
Well, that's why God invented teleprompters!
Shouldn't he rehearse, or something?
No can do, we're live in 10, 9--
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
I-I... I can't do this.
No, not again.
I-I haven't performed since--
Blitzø, if your performance on stage is
half as good as it is in bed,
you'll leave them breathless.
Now, hurry up and wow them,
so we can get back to finding Via.
Break a leg, darling!
Action!
Well, if it isn't our neighbor, Ronnie.
You feel that earthquake earlier?
Say something...
Oh, yea? Yeah.
"That was just my wife rolling out of bed."
Yeah, yeah!
Yeah, and then that bitch hit her head
on the way down and shattered her skull!
There's blood everywhere...
pee in her pants...
♪Don't wanna do what my daddy told me to♪
♪On the edge, tryna see a brand new view♪
♪Woah, and I liked that♪
♪Sick and tired of just wastin' all my time♪
♪You know, what?
I'll just go commit a crime, woah♪
♪And I like it♪
♪Yeah, yeah, yeah♪
♪Oh, no♪
♪Woah, woah♪
♪And I like it♪
♪Wanna see the sights♪
♪Be a troublemaker♪
♪Turn off the lights♪
♪Get in a fight♪
♪Live on long
I'm not a faker♪
♪I'm a product of a broken home♪
♪And know that I can make it on my own♪
♪A story I will write♪
♪And, going off the radar♪
♪And I like it♪
Oh, Uggie!
You've gone and done it again.
That's the fifth couch this year!
You know, maybe it's about time I found you a new home,
one that could put up with your attitude.
I could take him, Mr. Ronnie!
I'd be happy to adopt old Uggie and give him the attention he needs!
Yeah...
yeah, m-maybe, you should adopt...
Aww, they're all so cute.
And they're.... sad.
Maybe you could adopt this one here.
Quite a strong lad, he'll be perfect for whatever work you want to use him for.
Ugh! No, I'm not looking for no ugly wonker, heh.
I need something that's more family-friendly.
A gift for the wife, huh?
No problem.
We have a nice selection for other hounds.
Who's that?
Oh, her?
That's just Loona. What a nightmare.
Serious attitude problems.
She'll be out of our hair next month when she ages out.
Good riddance, if you ask me.
She'll never amount to anything much.
No. No, no, no, you can't have her!
She's mine, and I love her!
But, Mr. Ronnie, you gotta let me have the puppy.
You just gotta!
Don't you touch her, you little anal fissure!
Oh, you think this is funny, assholes?!
She’s not fit to be a mother!
I saw her doing lines of coke in her dressing room!
Now, uh... Ronnie.
I think maybe you should--
No! You can't have my baby, bitch!
I'LL NEVER GET RID OF HER!
I'm coming, Bliiiitzø!
Excuse me! Would you mind?!
Now, let's go find our daughters.
Hey.
How did you find me?
Your Sinstagram.
Nice pics by the way.
Oh, thanks.
You okay?
Can't believe I was so stupid.
I spent all day looking for a place where
I could see some dumb meteor shower.
And all I get is... this!
Yeah, smog's a bitch.
You know, your dad's really worried about you.
Right! That's why you're here instead of him.
He couldn't be bothered to keep his promise,
and now he can't be bothered to come and get me himself.
He'd rather spend his time just screaming at my mum.
Why does he hates her more than he loves me?
Sometimes...
sometimes it's not as simple as that.
This kind of shit gets messy, and everybody's got issues,
especially dads.
And sometimes they fuck up --
well, all the time.
But, that doesn't mean they don't care.
If he cares, where is he?
He's somewhere down there.
He's here?
Looking for you.
I mean...
try to cut your dad some slack.
He may not always get it right, but...
he's trying.
That's more important than you think.
You ready to go?
Yeah.
Now, if we could just find where...
Loona!
Oh, Loona, my sweet baby girl!
I'm so sorry, I'll never replace you no matter what you--
You're good.
Dad... I'm so sorry.
I'm just relieved you're okay!
But, what would possess you to do such a thing?
You know I haven't taught you spells like this yet.
I just wanted to see the stars you promised.
The stars?
Azathoth's tears!
Oh, no. Oh, my dear sweet Via.
I am so--
I know, dad.
It's okay, you're here now.
What the fuck is that?
My acting career.
Look at that one!
Did you see that one?
Now, where the fuck are M n' M?
Art is heavy!
March, mister!